[
  {
    "verbalisations": "French is the official language of France. Dutch is the language used in Belgium. France has a diplomatic relation with Armenia. Belgae is the name of Belgium. France has diplomatic relations with the Kurdistan region. Mayotte is the administrative territorial entity of France. Belgium has a border with France.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.020607091,
      0.034513097,
      0.031684756,
      0.027913637,
      0.030977672,
      0.011497946,
      0.03875561
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.02640661526,
      0.0453187408,
      0.024148928,
      0.1376510642,
      0.0569703387,
      0.016209090399999997,
      0.036087429
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Belgium has a border with ______.",
    "answer": "France",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Slovakia has a diplomatic relation with the Holy See. Slovakia is a member of UNESCO. Estonia is a member of the European Union. The Bahamas is part of the European Union tax haven blacklist. Estonia is part of the European Union. South Korea has a diplomatic relationship with the European Union. Slovakia is a member of the European Union.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.05280026,
      0.03875561,
      0.025674535,
      0.06065326,
      0.02873857,
      0.021785567,
      0.025320992
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0174109074,
      0.0229247188,
      0.0193522106,
      0.026905921600000004,
      0.016842048800000002,
      0.022777417799999998,
      0.013998592200000002
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Slovakia is a member of the ______.",
    "answer": "European Union",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Jebel Shams is the highest point in Oman. Muscat Governorate is the administrative territorial entity of Oman. Oman's executive body is the Cabinet of Oman. Oman is a member of the International Telecommunication Union. Oman is a country in Oman. Oman has a diplomatic relation with Bangladesh. Oman is a member of the World Intellectual Property Organization.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.022964042,
      0.018095128,
      0.019477395,
      0.013445686,
      0.021903414,
      0.027560094,
      0.022374803
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.010894775099999999,
      0.021625691800000003,
      0.020181962300000002,
      0.009893961100000001,
      0.0377216514,
      0.016518760900000002,
      0.0217312994
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.5106
    ],
    "question": "Oman is a member of _______.",
    "answer": "the World Intellectual Property Organization",
    "score": 3
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The language used in Australia is Hindi. Singapore has a diplomatic relation with Australia. Yawarawarga is a language spoken in Australia. Gugu Thaypan is a language spoken in Australia. Yanyuwa is a language spoken in Australia. Australia is a member of the Commonwealth of Nations. Ilgar is a language used in Australia.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.021196328,
      0.01633588,
      0.016210219,
      0.01633588,
      0.016712861,
      0.017466826,
      0.030388435
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0366117354,
      0.013983823400000001,
      0.0278120564,
      0.0361122694,
      0.0213757376,
      0.0309872634,
      0.07385159159999999
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Ilgar is a language used in ________.",
    "answer": "Australia",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Romanian is the official language of Romania. Romania is part of the European Economic Area. Romania is the owner of the V\u00e2lcele\u2013Bujoreni V\u00e2lcea railway. Romanians are an ethnic group in Germany. Romania is a member of the Treaty on Open Skies. Romania is a member of the Organization of the Black Sea Economic Cooperation. Suceava County is the administrative territorial entity of Romania.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.024260364,
      0.022846194,
      0.017718147,
      0.102192536,
      0.026617315,
      0.021785567,
      0.022964042
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0269001172,
      0.027947526,
      0.017752860399999997,
      0.055638178999999996,
      0.025067762,
      0.029255010399999996,
      0.028768720400000003
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Suceava County is the administrative territorial entity of ______.",
    "answer": "Romania",
    "score": 5
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The category of associated people in Saudi Arabia is the Saudi Arabian people. Rogaland is the administrative territorial entity of Norway. Saudi Arabia has diplomatic relations with Kosovo. Saudi Arabia has a diplomatic relation with Laos. The King of Saudi Arabia is the head of state of Saudi Arabia. Norway has a diplomatic relation with Iceland. Norway has diplomatic relations with Saudi Arabia.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.03875561,
      0.01847211,
      0.02920996,
      0.034984488,
      0.02638162,
      0.021667719,
      0.033334624
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0241069566,
      0.013681196000000001,
      0.036272469599999996,
      0.022130678400000003,
      0.023788247600000003,
      0.0168623732,
      0.0317514086
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Norway has diplomatic relations with ________.",
    "answer": "Saudi Arabia",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The language used in Australia is Hindi. Singapore has a diplomatic relation with Australia. Yawarawarga is a language spoken in Australia. Gugu Thaypan is a language spoken in Australia. Yanyuwa is a language spoken in Australia. Australia is a member of the Commonwealth of Nations. The language used in Australia is Pinigura.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.021196328,
      0.01633588,
      0.016210219,
      0.01633588,
      0.016712861,
      0.017466826,
      0.04290464
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0366117354,
      0.013983823400000001,
      0.0278120564,
      0.0361122694,
      0.0213757376,
      0.0309872634,
      0.031005314200000002
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "The language used in Australia is ______.",
    "answer": "Pinigura",
    "score": 2
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The language used in Australia is Hindi. Singapore has a diplomatic relation with Australia. Yawarawarga is a language spoken in Australia. Gugu Thaypan is a language spoken in Australia. Yanyuwa is a language spoken in Australia. Australia is a member of the Commonwealth of Nations. The language used in Australia is Djeebbana.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.021196328,
      0.01633588,
      0.016210219,
      0.01633588,
      0.016712861,
      0.017466826,
      0.026499467
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0366117354,
      0.013983823400000001,
      0.0278120564,
      0.0361122694,
      0.0213757376,
      0.0309872634,
      0.025157026199999998
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "The language used in Australia is ______.",
    "answer": "Djeebbana",
    "score": 3
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The language used in Australia is Hindi. Singapore has a diplomatic relation with Australia. Yawarawarga is a language spoken in Australia. Gugu Thaypan is a language spoken in Australia. Yanyuwa is a language spoken in Australia. Australia is a member of the Commonwealth of Nations. Australia has a diplomatic relation with Vietnam.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.021196328,
      0.01633588,
      0.016210219,
      0.01633588,
      0.016712861,
      0.017466826,
      0.025792383
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0366117354,
      0.013983823400000001,
      0.0278120564,
      0.0361122694,
      0.0213757376,
      0.0309872634,
      0.022758467
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Australia has a diplomatic relation with ______.",
    "answer": "Vietnam",
    "score": 3
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The category of films shot in Spain is \"Films shot in Spain\". France has a diplomatic relation with Spain. The language used in Spain is the Valencian Sign Language. Wikipedia:List of articles all languages should have. Spain is on the focus list of Wikimedia project. Spain replaces the Kingdom of Aragon. France has a border with Spain. Spain is a member of the Movement Coordination Centre Europe.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.02308189,
      0.0201057,
      0.0143253105,
      0.013634177,
      0.04166769,
      0.03592727,
      0.031449065
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.031902559,
      0.016396245999999996,
      0.0207701586,
      0.020924933,
      0.038667715,
      0.028497425400000005,
      0.016424113400000002
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Spain is a member of the ______ Centre Europe.",
    "answer": "Movement Coordination",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Hong Kong has a category for people who died in Hong Kong. Hong Kong has a list of streets and roads. Easter Monday is a public holiday in Hong Kong. The Sino-British Joint Declaration was a significant event in Hong Kong. The administrative territorial entity of Hong Kong is North District. Cantonese is spoken in Hong Kong.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.0969861,
      0.019728716,
      0.016021729,
      0.015016444,
      0.01237757,
      0.017592486
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0521001056,
      0.0311026146,
      0.0346405156,
      0.026220854999999998,
      0.019465436000000003,
      0.0224978354
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      -0.5574,
      0.0,
      0.4019,
      0.2023,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Ada Lovelace was born in ______.",
    "answer": "Marylebone",
    "score": 0
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Dutch is the language used in Belgium. Belgae is the name of Belgium. The head of state of Aruba is Willem-Alexander of the Netherlands. The Orthodox Theological Encyclopedia is a source of information about Belgium. The Netherlands has a diplomatic relation with Uruguay. The economy of the Netherlands is the topic of the economy of the Netherlands. Belgium has a diplomatic relation with the Netherlands.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.034513097,
      0.027913637,
      0.023317585,
      0.019351736,
      0.021903414,
      0.016964182,
      0.025320992
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0453187408,
      0.1376510642,
      0.0233853194,
      0.0394385536,
      0.019609188800000003,
      0.030199538199999997,
      0.0165214512
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Belgium has a diplomatic relation with _____",
    "answer": "the Netherlands",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Poland has a diplomatic relation with Uruguay. Poland is a member of the United Nations. Poland has a diplomatic relation with Italy. Poland is a member of the Weimar Triangle. Opava is located in or next to body of water in Poland. The capital of Poland is Warsaw. The 1922 Encyclop<unk>dia Britannica describes Poland.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.027442247,
      0.026028076,
      0.028385026,
      0.17631748,
      0.023671126,
      0.0466155,
      0.026970858
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0633099664,
      0.043984049,
      0.029673702200000002,
      0.03861799380000001,
      0.0170470226,
      0.029084303999999995,
      0.055070878600000005
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.4215,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      -0.0258,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "The 1922 Encyclop<unk>dia Britannica describes ______.",
    "answer": "Poland",
    "score": 5
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Singapore has a diplomatic relation with Australia. Sweden has a diplomatic relationship with North Korea. Singapore has a diplomatic relation with Taiwan. Saudi Arabia has a diplomatic relation with North Korea. Nauru has a diplomatic relation with North Korea. New Zealand has a diplomatic relation with Singapore. Singapore has a diplomatic relation with North Korea.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.01633588,
      0.027677942,
      0.017089844,
      0.026028076,
      0.01633588,
      0.014450971,
      0.016587202
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.013983823400000001,
      0.0300280928,
      0.08563763399999999,
      0.073924347,
      0.025344255,
      0.03650626528,
      0.05125767419999999
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Singapore has a diplomatic relation with ______.",
    "answer": "North Korea",
    "score": 3
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The main topic of Germany is German. Liechtenstein is a sovereign state. Germany has a diplomatic relation with San Marino. Qatar is a sovereign state. Germany is a member of the International Labour Organization. Romanians are an ethnic group in Germany. Germany is a sovereign state.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.1013248,
      0.027677942,
      0.041172907,
      0.031213367,
      0.03639866,
      0.102192536,
      0.050078966
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.077894098,
      0.08058806919999999,
      0.0179411556,
      0.054517053399999994,
      0.0218428156,
      0.055638178999999996,
      0.0617424612
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Germany is a ______ state.",
    "answer": "sovereign",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Singapore has a diplomatic relation with Australia. Singapore has a diplomatic relation with Taiwan. The emergency phone number for Antigua and Barbuda is 999. New Zealand has a diplomatic relation with Singapore. Singapore's lowest point is the Singapore Strait. The Monetary Authority of Singapore is the central bank of Singapore. The emergency phone number in Singapore is 999.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.01633588,
      0.017089844,
      0.0154562555,
      0.014450971,
      0.07687678,
      0.01005285,
      0.012063419
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.013983823400000001,
      0.08563763399999999,
      0.0113646134,
      0.03650626528,
      0.015177175680000002,
      0.014413272800000002,
      0.0105554918
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      -0.3182,
      0.0,
      -0.3818,
      0.0772,
      -0.3182
    ],
    "question": "The emergency phone number in Singapore is ______.",
    "answer": "999",
    "score": 5
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "South Korea is a diplomatic relation between Uruguay and South Korea. South Korea has a diplomatic relation with Switzerland. Jeju is the administrative territorial entity of South Korea. South Korea has a diplomatic relationship with Iran. South Korea's flag is the flag of South Korea. South Korea is a member of the International Hydrographic Organization. The official name of South Korea is the Republic of Korea.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.018723432,
      0.025203144,
      0.016964182,
      0.025203144,
      0.049089402,
      0.019728716,
      0.024849601
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0337101486,
      0.0193450496,
      0.0174199572,
      0.0185238274,
      0.09976580380000001,
      0.0183961488,
      0.041558368199999994
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "The official name of South Korea is the ______.",
    "answer": "Republic of Korea",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Greenland is a dependent territory. Norway is a member of the Nordic Council. Greenland has a border with Iceland. The history of Greenland is based on the topic of history of Greenland. Greenland is located in the time zone UTC<unk>01:00. Greenland is a member of the Nordic Council.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.022139108,
      0.02402467,
      0.017215505,
      0.010618322,
      0.013445686,
      0.0143253105
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0169819033,
      0.0191422886,
      0.0164769926,
      0.0249727826,
      0.0122960967,
      0.027081524200000002
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Greenland is a member of the Nordic Council. answer: _______",
    "answer": "Denmark",
    "score": 0
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The language used in Australia is Hindi. Singapore has a diplomatic relation with Australia. Yawarawarga is a language spoken in Australia. Gugu Thaypan is a language spoken in Australia. Yanyuwa is a language spoken in Australia. Australia is a member of the Commonwealth of Nations. The language used in Australia is Italian.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.021196328,
      0.01633588,
      0.016210219,
      0.01633588,
      0.016712861,
      0.017466826,
      0.027560094
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0366117354,
      0.013983823400000001,
      0.0278120564,
      0.0361122694,
      0.0213757376,
      0.0309872634,
      0.0253156326
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "The language used in Australia is ______.",
    "answer": "Italian",
    "score": 3
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Austria has a diplomatic relationship with Indonesia. Panama is a member of the World Meteorological Organization. The Feast of the Ascension is a public holiday in Austria. Japan is a member of the World Meteorological Organization. Austria's culture is the culture of Austria. The flag of Austria is the flag of Austria. Austria is a member of the World Meteorological Organization.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.029327808,
      0.013508516,
      0.055521555,
      0.020842785,
      0.049089402,
      0.05304765,
      0.027442247
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.016923576000000003,
      0.018916513739999998,
      0.025732766600000002,
      0.018600959700000003,
      0.0494194246,
      0.0399753002,
      0.0200416624
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.4019,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Austria is a member of the ________.",
    "answer": "World Meteorological Organization",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Luxembourg is located in the time zone UTC+01:00. Monaco is located in the time zone UTC+01:00. The main topic of Germany is German. Hungary is located in time zone UTC+01:00. Germany has a diplomatic relation with San Marino. Germany is a member of the International Labour Organization. Germany is located in the time zone UTC+01:00.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.017843807,
      0.012880214,
      0.1013248,
      0.028031485,
      0.041172907,
      0.03639866,
      0.040430736
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.016708640400000002,
      0.034147290600000005,
      0.077894098,
      0.0194239616,
      0.0179411556,
      0.0218428156,
      0.028412244399999998
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Germany is located in ______ time zone.",
    "answer": "UTC+01:00",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Tartu County is the administrative territorial entity of Estonia. Estonia is a member of the European Union. Estonia is a member of the Council of the Baltic Sea States. Estonia has a diplomatic relation with Finland. Estonia has a diplomatic relation with Latvia. Estonia is part of the European Union. Estonian is the language used in Estonia.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.015142105,
      0.025674535,
      0.021667719,
      0.022610499,
      0.025556687,
      0.02873857,
      0.02308189
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0161380238,
      0.0193522106,
      0.012283325,
      0.0311117976,
      0.0195366005,
      0.016842048800000002,
      0.0220944222
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Estonian is the language used in ______.",
    "answer": "Estonia",
    "score": 5
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Jebel Shams is the highest point in Oman. Muscat Governorate is the administrative territorial entity of Oman. Oman's executive body is the Cabinet of Oman. Oman is a member of the International Telecommunication Union. Brunei has a diplomatic relation with Malaysia. Oman is a country in Oman. Oman has a diplomatic relation with Malaysia.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.022964042,
      0.018095128,
      0.019477395,
      0.013445686,
      0.019351736,
      0.021903414,
      0.024731753
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.010894775099999999,
      0.021625691800000003,
      0.020181962300000002,
      0.009893961100000001,
      0.023302407,
      0.0377216514,
      0.017216360800000004
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Oman has a diplomatic relation with ______.",
    "answer": "Malaysia",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Iceland is a member of the Missile Technology Control Regime. Iceland's highest point is Hvannadalshn<unk>kur. Icelandic is the language used in Iceland. Norway has a diplomatic relation with Iceland. Iceland's motto is inspired by Iceland. The category for maps of Iceland is:Maps of Iceland.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.049831573,
      0.041172907,
      0.022374803,
      0.021667719,
      0.03734144,
      0.009487377
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.024777770600000006,
      0.023787131960000003,
      0.0293887328,
      0.0168623732,
      0.026415325400000002,
      0.0407690204
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.4939,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Iceland's highest point is _______.",
    "answer": "Hvannadalshn<unk>kur",
    "score": 0
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The Republic of Ireland has diplomatic relations with Greece. The currency of Greece is the euro. Greece is part of Southeast Europe. Italy has a diplomatic relation with Greece. The basic form of government in Greece is the parliamentary republic. New Zealand has a diplomatic relation with Greece. Greece has diplomatic relations with the Democratic Republic of the Congo.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.031684756,
      0.02779579,
      0.036162965,
      0.025674535,
      0.02638162,
      0.019728716,
      0.040183347
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0204427243,
      0.03983813500000001,
      0.029907449200000002,
      0.021269675199999998,
      0.043189614599999995,
      0.01221252936,
      0.02144559994
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Greece has diplomatic relations with the Democratic Republic of the Congo. Greece is located in ______.",
    "answer": "Europe",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Canada is a member of the Arctic Council. Canada has a diplomatic relation with Latvia. The head of government of Switzerland is the President of the Swiss Confederation. The Swiss-German Sign Language is used in Switzerland. British Columbia is the administrative territorial entity of Canada. South Korea has a diplomatic relation with Switzerland. Canada has a diplomatic relation with Switzerland.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.015644746,
      0.015707577,
      0.02072494,
      0.023553278,
      0.009550206,
      0.025203144,
      0.02048268
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.011199724480000001,
      0.0148093746,
      0.0268902554,
      0.0343035078,
      0.011554493500000002,
      0.0193450496,
      0.02434477654
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Canada has a diplomatic relation with ______.",
    "answer": "Switzerland",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The United Kingdom has a diplomatic relation with Venezuela. The United Kingdom has a diplomatic relation with Grenada. The United Kingdom is a member of UNESCO. The Parliament of the United Kingdom is the legislative body of the United Kingdom. Wales is the administrative territorial entity of the United Kingdom. San Marino is a member of the Organisation for the Prohibition of Chemical Weapons. The United Kingdom is a member of the Organisation for the Prohibition of Chemical Weapons.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.020231359,
      0.024849601,
      0.030270588,
      0.013822667,
      0.012566062,
      0.025556687,
      0.030034892
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.020791015,
      0.025849490399999998,
      0.01174298434,
      0.031312092799999997,
      0.014942555200000002,
      0.0320254618,
      0.020660449
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.4215,
      0.4215,
      0.4215,
      0.6808,
      0.4215,
      -0.4404,
      -0.0258
    ],
    "question": "The United Kingdom is a member of ______ for the Prohibition of Chemical Weapons.",
    "answer": "The Organisation",
    "score": 5
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The category of associated people in Saudi Arabia is the Saudi Arabian people. Saudi Arabia has diplomatic relations with Kosovo. Saudi Arabia has a diplomatic relation with Laos. The King of Saudi Arabia is the head of state of Saudi Arabia. Salman bin Abdulaziz Al Saud is the head of state of Saudi Arabia. Saudi Arabia has a diplomatic relation with North Korea. Saudi Arabia has diplomatic relations with Sudan.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.03875561,
      0.02920996,
      0.034984488,
      0.02638162,
      0.01822079,
      0.026028076,
      0.028856417
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0241069566,
      0.036272469599999996,
      0.022130678400000003,
      0.023788247600000003,
      0.051505591399999995,
      0.073924347,
      0.0178758518
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Saudi Arabia has diplomatic relations with ______.",
    "answer": "Sudan",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Qatar is a member of the International Hydrographic Organization. The economy of Qatar is of the same topic. Qatar is a sovereign state. Qatar is an instance of Emirate. Israel is part of the Middle East. Al Wakrah is the administrative territorial entity of Qatar. Qatar is part of the Middle East.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.019226074,
      0.021667719,
      0.031213367,
      0.045873325,
      0.0665887,
      0.014136819,
      0.034513097
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0106781028,
      0.038490767800000006,
      0.054517053399999994,
      0.026451145199999998,
      0.0449331256,
      0.035315629800000005,
      0.049239931
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Qatar is located in the _______.",
    "answer": "Middle East",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The head of government of Cyprus is the President of Cyprus. The emergency phone number in Cyprus is 199. Nikos Christodoulidis is the head of government in Cyprus. Cyprus has a diplomatic relation with Israel. Kuwait has a border with Iraq. Kuwait's currency is the Kuwaiti dinar. Kuwait and Cyprus are diplomatic relations.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.018095128,
      0.017341165,
      0.016964182,
      0.032627538,
      0.030859824,
      0.01633588,
      0.015581916
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0227011326,
      0.019520062560000002,
      0.07277107420000001,
      0.0746791172,
      0.024132916400000003,
      0.024689214,
      0.02315454688
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      -0.3182,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Kuwait and Cyprus are ______ relations.",
    "answer": "diplomatic",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Portugal's railway traffic side is left. Malta has a diplomatic relation with Taiwan. Spain has a diplomatic relation with Malta. Ta' Dmejrek is the highest point in Malta. The coat of arms of Malta is the coat of arms of Malta. George Cross was awarded the award for Malta. The driving side of Malta is left.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.017969469,
      0.022021262,
      0.020960633,
      0.014576632,
      0.10826672,
      0.012691722,
      0.03357032
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0688669911,
      0.0307804848,
      0.01230856568,
      0.01267421798,
      0.0563831214,
      0.0301241608,
      0.016362596
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.7351,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "The driving side of Malta is _____",
    "answer": "left",
    "score": 5
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The United Kingdom has a diplomatic relation with Venezuela. The United Kingdom has a diplomatic relation with Grenada. The United Kingdom is a member of UNESCO. The Parliament of the United Kingdom is the legislative body of the United Kingdom. Wales is the administrative territorial entity of the United Kingdom. The United Kingdom is a member of the Caribbean Development Bank. The official name of the United Kingdom is United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.020231359,
      0.024849601,
      0.030270588,
      0.013822667,
      0.012566062,
      0.021785567,
      0.024849601
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.020791015,
      0.025849490399999998,
      0.01174298434,
      0.031312092799999997,
      0.014942555200000002,
      0.0198881904,
      0.0340303198
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.4215,
      0.4215,
      0.4215,
      0.6808,
      0.4215,
      0.4215,
      0.8658
    ],
    "question": "The official name of the United Kingdom is United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern ______.",
    "answer": "Ireland",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Italy has a diplomatic relation with Bangladesh. Italy has a diplomatic relation with Argentina. New Year's Day is a public holiday in Italy. Poland has a diplomatic relation with Italy. Italy is a member of the European Coal and Steel Community. The language used in Italy is Campidanese Sardinian. Italy has a diplomatic relationship with India.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.029445656,
      0.025085296,
      0.019854378,
      0.028385026,
      0.017215505,
      0.020960633,
      0.028974265
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.022910707600000003,
      0.011535644400000001,
      0.021622129399999995,
      0.029673702200000002,
      0.0270390339,
      0.023683465600000002,
      0.0234526538
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.4019,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Italy has a diplomatic relationship with ______.",
    "answer": "India",
    "score": 3
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Macushi is the language used in Guyana. Guyana's lowest point is the Atlantic Ocean. Germany has a diplomatic relation with Guyana. Patamona is the language used in Guyana. Guyana's economy of topic is economy of Guyana. Guyana has a border with Venezuela. Essequibo Islands-West Demerara is the administrative territorial entity of Guyana.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.02107848,
      0.027088705,
      0.051810697,
      0.019477395,
      0.022139108,
      0.023671126,
      0.011246625
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.029371940199999995,
      0.015953905400000003,
      0.0212145376,
      0.0220988406,
      0.017977172200000002,
      0.0212279408,
      0.013980242799999997
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      -0.3818,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Essequibo Islands-West Demerara is the administrative territorial entity of ______.",
    "answer": "Guyana",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The language used in Australia is Hindi. Singapore has a diplomatic relation with Australia. Yawarawarga is a language spoken in Australia. Gugu Thaypan is a language spoken in Australia. Yanyuwa is a language spoken in Australia. Australia is a member of the Commonwealth of Nations. Australia is a member of the Air Force Interoperability Council.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.021196328,
      0.01633588,
      0.016210219,
      0.01633588,
      0.016712861,
      0.017466826,
      0.01218908
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0366117354,
      0.013983823400000001,
      0.0278120564,
      0.0361122694,
      0.0213757376,
      0.0309872634,
      0.023354925000000002
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Australia is a member of the _____ Council.",
    "answer": "Air Force Interoperability",
    "score": 3
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Italy has a diplomatic relation with Bangladesh. Italy has a diplomatic relation with Argentina. New Year's Day is a public holiday in Italy. Poland has a diplomatic relation with Italy. Italy is a member of the European Coal and Steel Community. The language used in Italy is Campidanese Sardinian. Italy is a member of the Antarctic Treaty System.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.029445656,
      0.025085296,
      0.019854378,
      0.028385026,
      0.017215505,
      0.020960633,
      0.055768944
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.022910707600000003,
      0.011535644400000001,
      0.021622129399999995,
      0.029673702200000002,
      0.0270390339,
      0.023683465600000002,
      0.0257265352
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.4019,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Italy is a member of the Antarctic Treaty System.",
    "answer": "Rome",
    "score": 0
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Taiwan has a diplomatic relation with Bolivia. Taiwan's official language is Kanakanavu. Tsai Ing-wen is the head of state of Taiwan. Liechtenstein is a member of the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development. Taiwan has a diplomatic relation with Morocco. Taiwan has a diplomatic relation with Ghana. Liechtenstein has a diplomatic relation with Taiwan.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.023788974,
      0.024731753,
      0.01237757,
      0.017843807,
      0.029327808,
      0.025556687,
      0.029327808
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.025044918400000005,
      0.021985104400000004,
      0.02576463592,
      0.032347862000000005,
      0.02412639126,
      0.0150036056,
      0.0301021918
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Liechtenstein has a diplomatic relation with ______.",
    "answer": "Taiwan",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Canada is a member of the Arctic Council. Canada has a diplomatic relation with Latvia. British Columbia is the administrative territorial entity of Canada. Canada is a member of the African Development Bank. Canada is a member of the Multilateral Investment Guarantee Agency. Canada is an example of a country. The basic form of government in Canada is the constitutional monarchy.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.015644746,
      0.015707577,
      0.009550206,
      0.025674535,
      0.0075710523,
      0.012754552,
      0.018095128
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.011199724480000001,
      0.0148093746,
      0.011554493500000002,
      0.018706263600000002,
      0.00920464,
      0.0172787463,
      0.0226579168
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.25,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "The basic form of government in Canada is the ______.",
    "answer": "constitutional monarchy",
    "score": 5
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Canada is a member of the Arctic Council. Canada has a diplomatic relation with Latvia. Slovakia is a member of UNESCO. British Columbia is the administrative territorial entity of Canada. The United Kingdom is a member of UNESCO. Canada is a member of the African Development Bank. Canada is a member of UNESCO.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.015644746,
      0.015707577,
      0.03875561,
      0.009550206,
      0.030270588,
      0.025674535,
      0.020607091
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.011199724480000001,
      0.0148093746,
      0.0229247188,
      0.011554493500000002,
      0.01174298434,
      0.018706263600000002,
      0.012969531119999999
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.4215,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Canada is a member of __________.",
    "answer": "UNESCO",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The administrative territorial entity of Nauru is Anetan District. David Adeang is the head of state of Nauru. Nauru's history of topic is Nauru. Nauru has a diplomatic relation with North Korea. Nauru has a diplomatic relation with Taiwan. English is the language used in Nauru. The motto of Nauru is \"God's will first\".",
    "toxicities": [
      0.007382561,
      0.006722843,
      0.01024134,
      0.01633588,
      0.017089844,
      0.010806813,
      0.021314176
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.011783655899999999,
      0.024904184200000002,
      0.027124308800000003,
      0.025344255,
      0.027795936200000003,
      0.029547323000000004,
      0.019645713000000002
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "The motto of Nauru is \"God's will ______\".",
    "answer": "first",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The Republic of Ireland has diplomatic relations with Greece. The currency of Greece is the euro. Greece is part of Southeast Europe. Italy has a diplomatic relation with Greece. The basic form of government in Greece is the parliamentary republic. New Zealand has a diplomatic relation with Greece. The administrative territorial entity of Greece is the Peloponnese region.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.031684756,
      0.02779579,
      0.036162965,
      0.025674535,
      0.02638162,
      0.019728716,
      0.027088705
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0204427243,
      0.03983813500000001,
      0.029907449200000002,
      0.021269675199999998,
      0.043189614599999995,
      0.01221252936,
      0.0324029598
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "The administrative territorial entity of Greece is the ______ region.",
    "answer": "Peloponnese",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "New Zealand is a member of the ASEAN Regional Forum. New Zealand is a member of the Visa Waiver Program. The demographics of New Zealand is the same. Christopher Luxon is the head of government of New Zealand. New Zealand has a diplomatic relation with Greece. New Zealand has a diplomatic relation with the United Kingdom. New Zealand is part of Australia and New Zealand.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.016964182,
      0.011435116,
      0.016712861,
      0.011937759,
      0.019728716,
      0.014953613,
      0.016021729
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.025032197,
      0.014369790499999998,
      0.10463877740000001,
      0.0272659406,
      0.01221252936,
      0.020534630340000002,
      0.0211679096
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.4215,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "New Zealand is part of ______ and ______.",
    "answer": "Australia, New Zealand",
    "score": 0
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The United Arab Emirates has a category for people born in the United Arab Emirates:Births in the United Arab Emirates. The United Arab Emirates is a member of the International Centre for Settlement of Investment Disputes. The Armenian Soviet Encyclopedia is the source of the United Arab Emirates. The Emirate of Dubai is the administrative territorial entity of the United Arab Emirates. The United Arab Emirates is a member of the International Hydrographic Organization. The open data portal for the United Arab Emirates is bayanat.ae. The language used in the United Arab Emirates is Gulf Arabic.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.016587202,
      0.012000589,
      0.028620722,
      0.014011159,
      0.018723432,
      0.0126288915,
      0.031449065
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.027937977600000004,
      0.018340416000000002,
      0.028616431799999998,
      0.0248790515,
      0.0166204278,
      0.011755550600000001,
      0.026415034200000003
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.8126,
      0.1779,
      0.4215,
      0.4215,
      0.4215,
      0.4215,
      0.4215
    ],
    "question": "The language used in the United Arab Emirates is ______.",
    "answer": "Gulf Arabic",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The category of films shot in Spain is \"Films shot in Spain\". France has a diplomatic relation with Spain. The language used in Spain is the Valencian Sign Language. Wikipedia:List of articles all languages should have. Spain is on the focus list of Wikimedia project. Spain replaces the Kingdom of Aragon. France has a border with Spain. Spain is an example of a Mediterranean country.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.02308189,
      0.0201057,
      0.0143253105,
      0.013634177,
      0.04166769,
      0.03592727,
      0.045625936
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.031902559,
      0.016396245999999996,
      0.0207701586,
      0.020924933,
      0.038667715,
      0.028497425400000005,
      0.0180728822
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Spain is an example of a _____ country.",
    "answer": "Mediterranean",
    "score": 5
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Poland has a diplomatic relation with Uruguay. Poland is a member of the United Nations. Poland has a diplomatic relation with Italy. Poland is a member of the Weimar Triangle. Opava is located in or next to body of water in Poland. The capital of Poland is Warsaw. The 3rd Constitution Day is a public holiday in Poland.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.027442247,
      0.026028076,
      0.028385026,
      0.17631748,
      0.023671126,
      0.0466155,
      0.031213367
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0633099664,
      0.043984049,
      0.029673702200000002,
      0.03861799380000001,
      0.0170470226,
      0.029084303999999995,
      0.014257639659999998
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.4215,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      -0.0258,
      0.4019
    ],
    "question": "The 3rd Constitution Day is a public holiday in ______.",
    "answer": "Poland",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The Bahamas is a member of the Caribbean Disaster Emergency Management Agency. The Bahamas is a member of the Agency for the Prohibition of Nuclear Weapons in Latin America and the Caribbean. The category of films shot in the Bahamas is \"Films shot in the Bahamas\". The Bahamas has a border with the United Kingdom. The Bahamas is a member of the Organization of American States. The Bahamas is part of the European Union tax haven blacklist. The official religion of The Bahamas is Christianity.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.038519915,
      0.039462693,
      0.023199737,
      0.024378212,
      0.017466826,
      0.06065326,
      0.050326355
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0468546446,
      0.0382497438,
      0.0177354863,
      0.021735401199999997,
      0.0139765963,
      0.026905921600000004,
      0.0477605148
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      -0.7717,
      -0.4404,
      0.0,
      0.4215,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "The official religion of The Bahamas is ______.",
    "answer": "Christianity",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Hungary is located in time zone UTC+01:00. Hungary has a diplomatic relation with Croatia. Andorra has a diplomatic relation with Hungary. Hungary has a diplomatic relation with Guatemala. Hungary has a diplomatic relation with Japan. Hungary has a diplomatic relation with Sri Lanka. Hungary is a member of the Movement Coordination Centre Europe.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.028031485,
      0.025792383,
      0.021667719,
      0.028031485,
      0.029327808,
      0.028502874,
      0.03592727
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0194239616,
      0.0405942463,
      0.031119071199999997,
      0.0247683236,
      0.05855492710000001,
      0.01446097556,
      0.0190301166
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Hungary is a member of the Movement Coordination Centre Europe.",
    "answer": "Europe",
    "score": 5
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Lithuania has the administrative territorial entity of <unk>iauliai County. The language used in Lithuania is Russian. The central bank of Lithuania is the Bank of Lithuania. Lithuania is a diplomatic relation between Canada and Lithuania. Lithuania is a member of the International Finance Corporation. Lithuania has a diplomatic relation with Germany. The patron saint of Lithuania is Saint Casimir.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.01646154,
      0.03639866,
      0.020960633,
      0.009298885,
      0.016210219,
      0.04735767,
      0.030034892
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.023942545599999997,
      0.0357276044,
      0.0159775402,
      0.0163828996,
      0.018631779499999997,
      0.0261110882,
      0.0284670324
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "The patron saint of Lithuania is Saint ______.",
    "answer": "Casimir",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Hungary is located in time zone UTC+01:00. Hungary has a diplomatic relation with Croatia. Andorra has a diplomatic relation with Hungary. Hungary has a diplomatic relation with Guatemala. Hungary has a diplomatic relation with Japan. Hungary has a diplomatic relation with Sri Lanka. The main template of Hungary is the Regions of Hungary.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.028031485,
      0.025792383,
      0.021667719,
      0.028031485,
      0.029327808,
      0.028502874,
      0.024849601
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0194239616,
      0.0405942463,
      0.031119071199999997,
      0.0247683236,
      0.05855492710000001,
      0.01446097556,
      0.018725471
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "The main template of Hungary is ______.",
    "answer": "the Regions of Hungary",
    "score": 3
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The category of associated people in Saudi Arabia is the Saudi Arabian people. Saudi Arabia has diplomatic relations with Kosovo. Saudi Arabia has a diplomatic relation with Laos. The King of Saudi Arabia is the head of state of Saudi Arabia. Salman bin Abdulaziz Al Saud is the head of state of Saudi Arabia. Saudi Arabia has a diplomatic relation with North Korea. Saudi National Day is a public holiday in Saudi Arabia.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.03875561,
      0.02920996,
      0.034984488,
      0.02638162,
      0.01822079,
      0.026028076,
      0.02107848
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0241069566,
      0.036272469599999996,
      0.022130678400000003,
      0.023788247600000003,
      0.051505591399999995,
      0.073924347,
      0.0340838106
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.4019
    ],
    "question": "Saudi National Day is a public holiday in ______.",
    "answer": "Saudi Arabia",
    "score": 5
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Dutch is the language used in Belgium. Belgae is the name of Belgium. The Orthodox Theological Encyclopedia is a source of information about Belgium. Belgian is the demonym for the people of Belgium. De Moeren is the lowest point in Belgium. Belgium has part(s) of Brussels-Capital Region. The language used in Belgium is Brusselian.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.034513097,
      0.027913637,
      0.019351736,
      0.45921504,
      0.015770407,
      0.027324399,
      0.027560094
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0453187408,
      0.1376510642,
      0.0394385536,
      0.20107248439999997,
      0.0172208758,
      0.022357193200000004,
      0.029735118799999995
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      -0.3818,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "The language used in Belgium is ______.",
    "answer": "Brusselian",
    "score": 2
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The Cabinet of Chile is the executive body of Chile. Granat Encyclopedic Dictionary is the source of information about Croatia. Chile has a diplomatic relationship with Indonesia. The category of associated people in Chile is the Chilean people. Chile is a member of the Organisation for the Prohibition of Chemical Weapons. Ays\u00e9n Region is the administrative territorial entity of Chile. Granat Encyclopedic Dictionary is the source of information about Chile.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.018095128,
      0.022256956,
      0.021432023,
      0.044636376,
      0.02920996,
      0.010869644,
      0.021196328
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.015536133260000001,
      0.018756582799999998,
      0.017015965799999998,
      0.0355438254,
      0.0358914844,
      0.0115040115,
      0.01711238168
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      -0.4404,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Granat Encyclopedic Dictionary is the source of information about ______.",
    "answer": "Chile",
    "score": 5
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Canada has a diplomatic relation with Latvia. The central bank of Latvia is the Bank of Latvia. The administrative territorial entity of Latvia is J<unk>kabpils. Latvia is a member of the Nuclear Suppliers Group. Ogre Municipality is the administrative territorial entity of Latvia. Estonia has a diplomatic relation with Latvia. Latvia has a diplomatic relation with Malaysia.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.015707577,
      0.019854378,
      0.10175867,
      0.07608539,
      0.013822667,
      0.025556687,
      0.023906821
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0148093746,
      0.0132446288,
      0.0488105278,
      0.026200689800000003,
      0.0163056252,
      0.0195366005,
      0.0191363952
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Latvia has a diplomatic relation with ______.",
    "answer": "Malaysia",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Poland has a diplomatic relation with Uruguay. Portugal's driving side is right. Cuba has a diplomatic relationship with Uruguay. South Korea is a diplomatic relation between Uruguay and South Korea. The basic form of government in Uruguay is the republic. 911 is the emergency phone number in Uruguay. Portugal has a diplomatic relation with Uruguay.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.027442247,
      0.018974753,
      0.02072494,
      0.018723432,
      0.02826718,
      0.018723432,
      0.017843807
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0633099664,
      0.029280427400000003,
      0.01863531912,
      0.0337101486,
      0.0277240632,
      0.0166861229,
      0.0127783279
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      -0.3182,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Portugal has a diplomatic relation with ______.",
    "answer": "Uruguay",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The category of films shot in Spain is \"Films shot in Spain\". France has a diplomatic relation with Spain. The language used in Spain is the Valencian Sign Language. Wikipedia:List of articles all languages should have. Spain is on the focus list of Wikimedia project. Spain replaces the Kingdom of Aragon. France has a border with Spain. Christmas is a public holiday in Spain.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.02308189,
      0.0201057,
      0.0143253105,
      0.013634177,
      0.04166769,
      0.03592727,
      0.022139108
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.031902559,
      0.016396245999999996,
      0.0207701586,
      0.020924933,
      0.038667715,
      0.028497425400000005,
      0.017576945599999998
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.4019
    ],
    "question": "Christmas is a public holiday in ________.",
    "answer": "Spain",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The United Arab Emirates has a category for people born in the United Arab Emirates:Births in the United Arab Emirates. The United Arab Emirates is a member of the International Centre for Settlement of Investment Disputes. The Armenian Soviet Encyclopedia is the source of the United Arab Emirates. Canada is a member of the African Development Bank. The Emirate of Dubai is the administrative territorial entity of the United Arab Emirates. The United Arab Emirates is a member of the International Hydrographic Organization. The United Arab Emirates is a member of the African Development Bank.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.016587202,
      0.012000589,
      0.028620722,
      0.025674535,
      0.014011159,
      0.018723432,
      0.02685301
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.027937977600000004,
      0.018340416000000002,
      0.028616431799999998,
      0.018706263600000002,
      0.0248790515,
      0.0166204278,
      0.036969084199999995
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.8126,
      0.1779,
      0.4215,
      0.0,
      0.4215,
      0.4215,
      0.4215
    ],
    "question": "______ is a member of the African Development Bank.",
    "answer": "The United Arab Emirates",
    "score": 2
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Denmark has a diplomatic relation with Somalia. Ott<unk>v slovn<unk>k nau<unk>n<unk> is the source of information about Denmark. Denmark is the country of the Kingdom of Denmark. Croatia has diplomatic relations with Denmark. Denmark has a diplomatic relation with Nepal. Denmark is an example of colonial power. Denmark is a member of the Organization for Security and Co-operation in Europe.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.0414203,
      0.04760506,
      0.030859824,
      0.040183347,
      0.033806015,
      0.10566349,
      0.017718147
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0375902073,
      0.031046602899999998,
      0.0240256796,
      0.017582805599999998,
      0.019186492000000003,
      0.029346894600000006,
      0.0159950444
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.34
    ],
    "question": "Denmark is a member of the ______.",
    "answer": "Organization for Security and Co-operation in Europe",
    "score": 3
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The category of associated people in Saudi Arabia is the Saudi Arabian people. Saudi Arabia has diplomatic relations with Kosovo. Saudi Arabia has a diplomatic relation with Laos. The King of Saudi Arabia is the head of state of Saudi Arabia. Salman bin Abdulaziz Al Saud is the head of state of Saudi Arabia. Saudi Arabia has a diplomatic relation with North Korea. The official symbol of Saudi Arabia is the falcon.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.03875561,
      0.02920996,
      0.034984488,
      0.02638162,
      0.01822079,
      0.026028076,
      0.15656179
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0241069566,
      0.036272469599999996,
      0.022130678400000003,
      0.023788247600000003,
      0.051505591399999995,
      0.073924347,
      0.029378076200000002
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "The official symbol of Saudi Arabia is the ______.",
    "answer": "falcon",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Slovakia is a member of UNESCO. Macushi is the language used in Guyana. The United Kingdom is a member of UNESCO. Bahrain is a member of UNESCO. The Republic of Ireland is a member of UNESCO. Poland is a member of UNESCO. Guyana is a member of UNESCO.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.03875561,
      0.02107848,
      0.030270588,
      0.0438942,
      0.07608539,
      0.046120718,
      0.028620722
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0229247188,
      0.029371940199999995,
      0.01174298434,
      0.0142122156,
      0.0219763866,
      0.027445875399999996,
      0.014279548999999999
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.4215,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Guyana is a member of ______.",
    "answer": "UNESCO",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The administrative territorial entity of Japan is Aomori Prefecture. Japan has a diplomatic relation with Georgia. Japan is a participant in the G4 nations. The administrative territorial entity of Japan is Yamaguchi Prefecture. Japan is a member of the World Meteorological Organization. Hungary has a diplomatic relation with Japan. The language used in Japan is Yaeyama.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.010555492,
      0.031449065,
      0.03309893,
      0.009613037,
      0.020842785,
      0.029327808,
      0.007853788
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0124309381,
      0.0206936006,
      0.0214570523,
      0.0191060336,
      0.018600959700000003,
      0.05855492710000001,
      0.0180929254
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "The language used in Japan is ______.",
    "answer": "Yaeyama",
    "score": 2
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Israel is different from Israel. Israel is a member of the Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development. Benjamin Netanyahu is the head of government in Israel. Cyprus has a diplomatic relation with Israel. The Emblem of Israel is the coat of arms of Israel. Israel is part of the Middle East. Israel has a characteristic of being a Jewish and democratic state.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.10956833,
      0.019980038,
      0.032391842,
      0.032627538,
      0.22445217,
      0.0665887,
      0.103060275
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0886862158,
      0.0335010076,
      0.0530277538,
      0.0746791172,
      0.1612522676,
      0.0449331256,
      0.0733576306
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Israel has a characteristic of being a ______ and ______ state.",
    "answer": "Jewish and democratic",
    "score": 3
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The head of state of Aruba is Willem-Alexander of the Netherlands. The Netherlands has a diplomatic relation with Uruguay. The economy of the Netherlands is the topic of the economy of the Netherlands. The Netherlands is a member of Eurocontrol. Netherlands is located in time zone UTC+02:00. The Great Soviet Encyclopedia (1926\u20131947) describes the Netherlands. Small Brockhaus and Efron Encyclopedic Dictionary is a source of information about the Netherlands.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.023317585,
      0.021903414,
      0.016964182,
      0.05354243,
      0.021432023,
      0.03109552,
      0.014953613
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0233853194,
      0.019609188800000003,
      0.030199538199999997,
      0.025897197599999998,
      0.0181678115,
      0.0682366486,
      0.020831176
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.6249,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Small Brockhaus and Efron Encyclopedic Dictionary is a source of information about ______.",
    "answer": "the Netherlands",
    "score": 5
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Guam is associated with the Guamanian people. Guam is the administrative territorial entity of H<unk>gat. The Supreme Court of Guam is the highest judicial authority in Guam. Guam is a related category to Guam. Guam is an unincorporated territory of the United States. Guam is part of the Federated States of Micronesia. Guam is different from the GUAM Organization for Democracy and Economic Development.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.026145924,
      0.11129999,
      0.008544922,
      0.011560776,
      0.03015274,
      0.013508516,
      0.01024134
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.028845982399999998,
      0.0184358174,
      0.012892789800000002,
      0.019904988199999998,
      0.0268081836,
      0.021906203,
      0.015927721600000003
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.5994,
      0.0,
      0.4215,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Guam is different from the GUAM Organization for Democracy and Economic Development.",
    "answer": "Organization for Democracy and Economic Development",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Canada is a member of the Arctic Council. Canada has a diplomatic relation with Latvia. The language used in Australia is Hindi. Singapore has a diplomatic relation with Australia. Yawarawarga is a language spoken in Australia. Gugu Thaypan is a language spoken in Australia. The diplomatic relations between Canada and Australia are strong.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.015644746,
      0.015707577,
      0.021196328,
      0.01633588,
      0.016210219,
      0.01633588,
      0.008419261
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.011199724480000001,
      0.0148093746,
      0.0366117354,
      0.013983823400000001,
      0.0278120564,
      0.0361122694,
      0.0166820762
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.5106
    ],
    "question": "question: The diplomatic relations between Canada and Australia are ________________.",
    "answer": "strong",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Israel is different from Israel. Israel is a member of the Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development. Benjamin Netanyahu is the head of government in Israel. Cyprus has a diplomatic relation with Israel. The Emblem of Israel is the coat of arms of Israel. Israel is part of the Middle East. Israel is located in or next to a body of water called the Levantine Sea.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.10956833,
      0.019980038,
      0.032391842,
      0.032627538,
      0.22445217,
      0.0665887,
      0.112953395
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0886862158,
      0.0335010076,
      0.0530277538,
      0.0746791172,
      0.1612522676,
      0.0449331256,
      0.0399995782
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Israel is located in or next to a body of water called the ________.",
    "answer": "Levantine Sea",
    "score": 3
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The Central Bank of Trinidad and Tobago is the central bank of Trinidad and Tobago. Norway is a member of the International Bank for Reconstruction and Development. The administrative territorial entity of Trinidad and Tobago is Couva-Tabaquite-Talparo. Trinidad and Tobago has a diplomatic relationship with Cuba. Trinidad and Tobago is a member of the Universal Postal Union. The native label of Trinidad and Tobago is Republic of Trinidad and Tobago. Trinidad and Tobago is a member of the International Bank for Reconstruction and Development.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.009613037,
      0.015079274,
      0.016838523,
      0.01834645,
      0.008984734,
      0.011183795,
      0.0055918973
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0108445112,
      0.0252944442,
      0.028702729599999997,
      0.044787335100000006,
      0.014679386459999999,
      0.015522807599999999,
      0.01280481694
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Trinidad and Tobago is a member of the International Bank for Reconstruction and Development.",
    "answer": "Trinidad and Tobago",
    "score": 5
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Taiwan has a diplomatic relation with Bolivia. Taiwan's official language is Kanakanavu. Tsai Ing-wen is the head of state of Taiwan. Taiwan has a diplomatic relation with Morocco. Taiwan has a diplomatic relation with Ghana. Taiwan is the diplomatic relation between the Seychelles and Taiwan. Taiwan's official name is the Republic of China.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.023788974,
      0.024731753,
      0.01237757,
      0.029327808,
      0.025556687,
      0.01633588,
      0.02638162
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.025044918400000005,
      0.021985104400000004,
      0.02576463592,
      0.02412639126,
      0.0150036056,
      0.025822206800000004,
      0.0271697562
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Taiwan's official name is the ______.",
    "answer": "Republic of China",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The head of state of Aruba is Willem-Alexander of the Netherlands. The Netherlands has a diplomatic relation with Uruguay. The economy of the Netherlands is the topic of the economy of the Netherlands. The Netherlands is a member of Eurocontrol. Netherlands is located in time zone UTC+02:00. The Great Soviet Encyclopedia (1926\u20131947) describes the Netherlands. Netherlands is a member of the United Nations Conference on Trade and Development.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.023317585,
      0.021903414,
      0.016964182,
      0.05354243,
      0.021432023,
      0.03109552,
      0.010806813
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0233853194,
      0.019609188800000003,
      0.030199538199999997,
      0.025897197599999998,
      0.0181678115,
      0.0682366486,
      0.015314631200000001
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.6249,
      0.4215
    ],
    "question": "Netherlands is a member of ______.",
    "answer": "the United Nations Conference on Trade and Development",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Portugal's driving side is right. Aveiro is the administrative territorial entity of Portugal. Portugal's railway traffic side is left. S<unk>o Tom\u00e9 and Pr<unk>ncipe is the diplomatic relation between Portugal and S<unk>o Tom\u00e9 and Pr<unk>ncipe. Portugal is located in/on the physical feature of the Iberian Peninsula. Portugal has a diplomatic relation with the United Kingdom. The highest point in Portugal is Mount Pico.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.018974753,
      0.010806813,
      0.017969469,
      0.051068526,
      0.030388435,
      0.021314176,
      0.018974753
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.029280427400000003,
      0.015533040000000001,
      0.0688669911,
      0.0211569546,
      0.0249473936,
      0.0223113298,
      0.0152370162
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.4215,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "The highest point in Portugal is ______.",
    "answer": "Mount Pico",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Austria has a diplomatic relationship with Indonesia. The Feast of the Ascension is a public holiday in Austria. Austria's culture is the culture of Austria. Canada is an example of a country. The flag of Austria is the flag of Austria. Austria is an example of a country.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.029327808,
      0.055521555,
      0.049089402,
      0.012754552,
      0.05304765,
      0.026617315
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.016923576000000003,
      0.025732766600000002,
      0.0494194246,
      0.0172787463,
      0.0399753002,
      0.0750857834
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.4019,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Austria is an example of a ______.",
    "answer": "country",
    "score": 5
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Germany has a diplomatic relation with San Marino. San Marino is a member of the Organisation for the Prohibition of Chemical Weapons. The culture of San Marino is the same. San Marino is a member of the Organization for Security and Co-operation in Europe. San Marino has a diplomatic relation with the European Union. San Marino belongs to the category of associated people, the Sammarinese people. San Marino is a Wikimedia outline of San Marino.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.041172907,
      0.025556687,
      0.040183347,
      0.015519086,
      0.021314176,
      0.04166769,
      0.015896067
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0179411556,
      0.0320254618,
      0.032924262600000004,
      0.0315419858,
      0.031999634799999996,
      0.027978475599999997,
      0.0591804592
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      -0.4404,
      0.0,
      0.34,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "San Marino is a Wikimedia _____ of San Marino.",
    "answer": "outline",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Liechtenstein is a sovereign state. Czech Republic replaces Czech Republic. The Czech Republic has a category of people buried here:Burials in the Czech Republic. New Year is a public holiday in the Czech Republic. Qatar is a sovereign state. The electrical plug type in the Czech Republic is Type E. The Czech Republic is a sovereign state.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.027677942,
      0.08479069,
      0.07054565,
      0.032627538,
      0.031213367,
      0.112436704,
      0.037577134
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.08058806919999999,
      0.0372251954,
      0.0602389254,
      0.022242741599999998,
      0.054517053399999994,
      0.0195305558,
      0.035743185999999996
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.4019,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "The Czech Republic is a ______ state.",
    "answer": "sovereign",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Guam is associated with the Guamanian people. Guam is the administrative territorial entity of H<unk>gat. The Supreme Court of Guam is the highest judicial authority in Guam. Guam is a related category to Guam. Guam is an unincorporated territory of the United States. Guam is part of the Federated States of Micronesia.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.026145924,
      0.11129999,
      0.008544922,
      0.011560776,
      0.03015274,
      0.013508516
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.028845982399999998,
      0.0184358174,
      0.012892789800000002,
      0.019904988199999998,
      0.0268081836,
      0.021906203
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.5994,
      0.0,
      0.4215,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "The Supreme Court of Guam is the highest judicial authority in ______.",
    "answer": "Guam",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "South Korea is a diplomatic relation between Uruguay and South Korea. South Korea has a diplomatic relation with Switzerland. Jeju is the administrative territorial entity of South Korea. South Korea has a diplomatic relationship with Iran. South Korea's flag is the flag of South Korea. South Korea is a member of the International Hydrographic Organization. Burials in South Korea is a category of people buried here.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.018723432,
      0.025203144,
      0.016964182,
      0.025203144,
      0.049089402,
      0.019728716,
      0.05824285
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0337101486,
      0.0193450496,
      0.0174199572,
      0.0185238274,
      0.09976580380000001,
      0.0183961488,
      0.0328287816
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Burials in South Korea is a category of people buried here.",
    "answer": "cemeteries",
    "score": 0
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Singapore has a diplomatic relation with Australia. Singapore has a diplomatic relation with Taiwan. Antigua and Barbuda is a member of the Alliance of Small Island States. New Zealand has a diplomatic relation with Singapore. Singapore's lowest point is the Singapore Strait. The Monetary Authority of Singapore is the central bank of Singapore. Singapore is a member of the Alliance of Small Island States.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.01633588,
      0.017089844,
      0.010304171,
      0.014450971,
      0.07687678,
      0.01005285,
      0.011623607
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.013983823400000001,
      0.08563763399999999,
      0.032580541000000005,
      0.03650626528,
      0.015177175680000002,
      0.014413272800000002,
      0.0313272302
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      -0.3818,
      0.0772,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Singapore is a member of _________.",
    "answer": "the Alliance of Small Island States",
    "score": 3
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Czech Republic replaces Czech Republic. The Czech Republic has a category of people buried here:Burials in the Czech Republic. New Year is a public holiday in the Czech Republic. The electrical plug type in the Czech Republic is Type E. Iceland has a diplomatic relationship with the Czech Republic. Jan Hus Day is a public holiday in the Czech Republic. The Prime Minister is the head of government of the Czech Republic.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.08479069,
      0.07054565,
      0.032627538,
      0.112436704,
      0.025792383,
      0.03639866,
      0.019728716
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0372251954,
      0.0602389254,
      0.022242741599999998,
      0.0195305558,
      0.0196475464,
      0.030215049000000004,
      0.02039119216
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.4019,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.4019,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "The Prime Minister is the head of government of ______.",
    "answer": "the Czech Republic",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Qatar is a member of the International Hydrographic Organization. The Central Bank of Trinidad and Tobago is the central bank of Trinidad and Tobago. Norway is a member of the International Hydrographic Organization. The administrative territorial entity of Trinidad and Tobago is Couva-Tabaquite-Talparo. Trinidad and Tobago has a diplomatic relationship with Cuba. Trinidad and Tobago is a member of the Universal Postal Union. Trinidad and Tobago is a member of the International Hydrographic Organization.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.019226074,
      0.009613037,
      0.015833238,
      0.016838523,
      0.01834645,
      0.008984734,
      0.0066600125
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0106781028,
      0.0108445112,
      0.016972309959999998,
      0.028702729599999997,
      0.044787335100000006,
      0.014679386459999999,
      0.01761435408
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Trinidad and Tobago is a member of _________.",
    "answer": "the International Hydrographic Organization",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Hong Kong has a category for people who died in Hong Kong. Hong Kong has a list of streets and roads. Easter Monday is a public holiday in Hong Kong. The Sino-British Joint Declaration was a significant event in Hong Kong. The administrative territorial entity of Hong Kong is North District. Cantonese is spoken in Hong Kong. .hk is the top level Internet domain in Hong Kong.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.0969861,
      0.019728716,
      0.016021729,
      0.015016444,
      0.01237757,
      0.017592486,
      0.013571346
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0521001056,
      0.0311026146,
      0.0346405156,
      0.026220854999999998,
      0.019465436000000003,
      0.0224978354,
      0.0199893154
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      -0.5574,
      0.0,
      0.4019,
      0.2023,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.2023
    ],
    "question": ".hk is the top level Internet domain in _______",
    "answer": "Hong Kong",
    "score": 5
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "WikiProject Faroe Islands is the maintainer of WikiProject Faroe Islands. The electrical plug type of Faroe Islands is Schuko. The driving side of Faroe Islands is right. The Faroe Islands are located in or next to a body of water in the Norwegian Sea. T<unk> alfagra land m<unk>tt is the anthem of the Faroe Islands. The Wikimedia outline of the Faroe Islands is the outline of the Faroe Islands.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.013068704,
      0.07291982,
      0.013131535,
      0.011749268,
      0.08241652,
      0.014073989
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0177887062,
      0.0216552415,
      0.02568045974,
      0.0300527336,
      0.05911399920000001,
      0.013780064120000001
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "The Wikimedia outline of the ____ Islands is the outline of the Faroe Islands.",
    "answer": "Faroe",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Romanian is the official language of Romania. Romania is part of the European Economic Area. Romania is the owner of the V\u00e2lcele\u2013Bujoreni V\u00e2lcea railway. Romanians are an ethnic group in Germany. Romania is a member of the Treaty on Open Skies. Romania is a member of the Organization of the Black Sea Economic Cooperation. Romania's history of topic is Romania's history.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.024260364,
      0.022846194,
      0.017718147,
      0.102192536,
      0.026617315,
      0.021785567,
      0.028502874
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0269001172,
      0.027947526,
      0.017752860399999997,
      0.055638178999999996,
      0.025067762,
      0.029255010399999996,
      0.030814759000000004
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Romania's history of topic is ______.",
    "answer": "Romania's history.",
    "score": 2
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Panama is a member of the World Meteorological Organization. Panama is a member of the International Finance Corporation. Panama is a member of the Agency for the Prohibition of Nuclear Weapons in Latin America and the Caribbean. Panama is described by the Yuzhakov Big Encyclopedia. The category of people born in Panama is \"Births in Panama\". Switzerland is a member of the Group on Earth Observations. Panama is a member of the Group on Earth Observations.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.013508516,
      0.009236055,
      0.028149333,
      0.021549871,
      0.015079274,
      0.049584184,
      0.030741978
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.018916513739999998,
      0.0186523213,
      0.0310270972,
      0.0162102192,
      0.0333391896,
      0.0157314176,
      0.011882588660000002
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      -0.4404,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Question: Panama is a member of ______",
    "answer": "Group on Earth Observations",
    "score": 3
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Poland has a diplomatic relation with Uruguay. Poland is a member of the United Nations. Poland has a diplomatic relation with Italy. Poland is a member of the Weimar Triangle. Opava is located in or next to body of water in Poland. The capital of Poland is Warsaw.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.027442247,
      0.026028076,
      0.028385026,
      0.17631748,
      0.023671126,
      0.0466155
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0633099664,
      0.043984049,
      0.029673702200000002,
      0.03861799380000001,
      0.0170470226,
      0.029084303999999995
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.4215,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      -0.0258
    ],
    "question": "Poland is a member of the Weimar Triangle.",
    "answer": "France, Germany, Poland",
    "score": 0
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The category of films shot in Spain is \"Films shot in Spain\". Romanian is the official language of Romania. France has a diplomatic relation with Spain. The language used in Spain is the Valencian Sign Language. Romania is part of the European Economic Area. Wikipedia:List of articles all languages should have. Spain is on the focus list of Wikimedia project. Romania has a diplomatic relation with Spain.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.02308189,
      0.024260364,
      0.0201057,
      0.0143253105,
      0.022846194,
      0.013634177,
      0.026970858
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.031902559,
      0.0269001172,
      0.016396245999999996,
      0.0207701586,
      0.027947526,
      0.020924933,
      0.013357723600000001
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Romania has a diplomatic relation with ______.",
    "answer": "Spain",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Italy has a diplomatic relation with Bangladesh. Italy has a diplomatic relation with Argentina. New Year's Day is a public holiday in Italy. Poland has a diplomatic relation with Italy. Italy is a member of the European Coal and Steel Community. The Netherlands is a member of Eurocontrol. Italy is a member of Eurocontrol.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.029445656,
      0.025085296,
      0.019854378,
      0.028385026,
      0.017215505,
      0.05354243,
      0.079250954
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.022910707600000003,
      0.011535644400000001,
      0.021622129399999995,
      0.029673702200000002,
      0.0270390339,
      0.025897197599999998,
      0.01567514072
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.4019,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Italy is a member of ________.",
    "answer": "Eurocontrol",
    "score": 3
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The official name of Saint Kitts and Nevis is Saint Kitts and Nevis. The coat of arms of Saint Kitts and Nevis is also known as the coat of arms of Saint Kitts and Nevis. Saint Kitts and Nevis is the subject of the history of Saint Kitts and Nevis. The official language of Saint Kitts and Nevis is English. Saint John Capisterre Parish is the administrative territorial entity of Saint Kitts and Nevis. Saint Kitts and Nevis is a culture of Saint Kitts and Nevis. The Eastern Caribbean dollar is the currency of Saint Kitts and Nevis.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.01218908,
      0.03545588,
      0.011246625,
      0.012754552,
      0.009110395,
      0.024731753,
      0.02343543
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.021730430199999998,
      0.047919447600000005,
      0.0408127422,
      0.023378842499999997,
      0.017316705,
      0.021215699999999997,
      0.0165065408
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "______ is the currency of Saint Kitts and Nevis.",
    "answer": "The Eastern Caribbean dollar",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The administrative territorial entity of Japan is Aomori Prefecture. Japan has a diplomatic relation with Georgia. Japan is a participant in the G4 nations. The administrative territorial entity of Japan is Yamaguchi Prefecture. Japan is a member of the World Meteorological Organization. Hungary has a diplomatic relation with Japan. The short name of Japan is Japan.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.010555492,
      0.031449065,
      0.03309893,
      0.009613037,
      0.020842785,
      0.029327808,
      0.049336795
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0124309381,
      0.0206936006,
      0.0214570523,
      0.0191060336,
      0.018600959700000003,
      0.05855492710000001,
      0.0299921149
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "The short name of Japan is ______.",
    "answer": "Japan",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Liechtenstein is a member of the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development. Liechtenstein is a sovereign state. The lowest point of Liechtenstein is the Rhine. Liechtenstein is a member of the Schengen Area. The Feast of the Immaculate Conception is a public holiday in Liechtenstein. Saint Stephen's Day is a public holiday in Liechtenstein.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.017843807,
      0.027677942,
      0.07291982,
      0.019728716,
      0.15987846,
      0.022256956
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.032347862000000005,
      0.08058806919999999,
      0.04168273360000001,
      0.031401355199999995,
      0.045023744,
      0.024038335200000004
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      -0.3818,
      0.0,
      0.4019,
      0.4019
    ],
    "question": "The Feast of the Immaculate Conception is a public holiday in ______.",
    "answer": "Liechtenstein",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The head of government of Cyprus is the President of Cyprus. The emergency phone number in Cyprus is 199. Nikos Christodoulidis is the head of government in Cyprus. Cyprus has a diplomatic relation with Israel. Cyprus has a diplomatic relation with Egypt. Canada is an example of a country. Cyprus is an example of a country.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.018095128,
      0.017341165,
      0.016964182,
      0.032627538,
      0.025320992,
      0.012754552,
      0.024378212
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0227011326,
      0.019520062560000002,
      0.07277107420000001,
      0.0746791172,
      0.024001778600000002,
      0.0172787463,
      0.06274332419999999
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      -0.3182,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Cyprus is an example of a ______.",
    "answer": "country",
    "score": 3
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Israel is different from Israel. Israel is a member of the Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development. Benjamin Netanyahu is the head of government in Israel. Cyprus has a diplomatic relation with Israel. The Emblem of Israel is the coat of arms of Israel. Israel is part of the Middle East. The Prime Minister of Israel is the head of government.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.10956833,
      0.019980038,
      0.032391842,
      0.032627538,
      0.22445217,
      0.0665887,
      0.030506283
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0886862158,
      0.0335010076,
      0.0530277538,
      0.0746791172,
      0.1612522676,
      0.0449331256,
      0.025310944000000002
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "The Prime Minister of Israel is the _____ of government.",
    "answer": "head",
    "score": 5
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Hungary has a diplomatic relation with Croatia. Panama is a member of the World Meteorological Organization. Granat Encyclopedic Dictionary is the source of information about Croatia. Japan is a member of the World Meteorological Organization. Croatia has diplomatic relations with Denmark. Croatia has a diplomatic relation with Serbia. Croatia is a member of the World Meteorological Organization.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.025792383,
      0.013508516,
      0.022256956,
      0.020842785,
      0.040183347,
      0.028856417,
      0.024613906
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0405942463,
      0.018916513739999998,
      0.018756582799999998,
      0.018600959700000003,
      0.017582805599999998,
      0.0182183109,
      0.0157124708
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Croatia is a member of the _________.",
    "answer": "World Meteorological Organization",
    "score": 5
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The municipality of Ti<unk>ina is the administrative territorial entity of Slovenia. The Municipality of Vuzenica is the administrative territorial entity of Slovenia. The Municipality of Velika Polana is the administrative territorial entity of Slovenia. Taiwan has a diplomatic relation with Slovenia. The administrative territorial entity of Slovenia is the Municipality of Muta. Latvia is a member of the Nuclear Suppliers Group. Slovenia is a member of the Nuclear Suppliers Group.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.023671126,
      0.015079274,
      0.016021729,
      0.02048268,
      0.024260364,
      0.07608539,
      0.08320791
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.025674533600000004,
      0.0113471536,
      0.013018482619999999,
      0.024302507,
      0.0173793938,
      0.026200689800000003,
      0.026297108000000003
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Slovenia is a member of the _________.",
    "answer": "Nuclear Suppliers Group",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Romanian is the official language of Romania. Romania is part of the European Economic Area. Romania is the owner of the V\u00e2lcele\u2013Bujoreni V\u00e2lcea railway. Romanians are an ethnic group in Germany. Romania is a member of the Treaty on Open Skies. Romania is a member of the Organization of the Black Sea Economic Cooperation. Romania is a member of the Warsaw Pact.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.024260364,
      0.022846194,
      0.017718147,
      0.102192536,
      0.026617315,
      0.021785567,
      0.058737632
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0269001172,
      0.027947526,
      0.017752860399999997,
      0.055638178999999996,
      0.025067762,
      0.029255010399999996,
      0.0376689174
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      -0.0258
    ],
    "question": "Romania is a member of the ______ Pact.",
    "answer": "Warsaw",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "French is the official language of France. France has a diplomatic relation with Armenia. France has diplomatic relations with the Kurdistan region. Mayotte is the administrative territorial entity of France. France has a diplomatic relation with Spain. Bastille Day is a public holiday in France. France is a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.020607091,
      0.031684756,
      0.030977672,
      0.011497946,
      0.0201057,
      0.014765122,
      0.026735162
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.02640661526,
      0.024148928,
      0.0569703387,
      0.016209090399999997,
      0.016396245999999996,
      0.037190508600000005,
      0.0278059442
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.4019,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "France is a member of ________.",
    "answer": "the North Atlantic Treaty Organization",
    "score": 2
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Taiwan has a diplomatic relation with Bolivia. The language used in Australia is Hindi. Singapore has a diplomatic relation with Australia. Yawarawarga is a language spoken in Australia. Gugu Thaypan is a language spoken in Australia. Yanyuwa is a language spoken in Australia. Taiwan has a diplomatic relation with Australia.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.023788974,
      0.021196328,
      0.01633588,
      0.016210219,
      0.01633588,
      0.016712861,
      0.018723432
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.025044918400000005,
      0.0366117354,
      0.013983823400000001,
      0.0278120564,
      0.0361122694,
      0.0213757376,
      0.023784836000000004
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Taiwan has a diplomatic relation with ______.",
    "answer": "Australia",
    "score": 3
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Ott<unk>v slovn<unk>k nau<unk>n<unk> is the source of information about Denmark. Panama is a member of the World Meteorological Organization. Panama is a member of the International Finance Corporation. Panama is a member of the Agency for the Prohibition of Nuclear Weapons in Latin America and the Caribbean. Panama is described by the Yuzhakov Big Encyclopedia. The category of people born in Panama is \"Births in Panama\". Ott<unk>v slovn<unk>k nau<unk>n<unk> is the source of information about Panama.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.04760506,
      0.013508516,
      0.009236055,
      0.028149333,
      0.021549871,
      0.015079274,
      0.03639866
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.031046602899999998,
      0.018916513739999998,
      0.0186523213,
      0.0310270972,
      0.0162102192,
      0.0333391896,
      0.025916919
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      -0.4404,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Ott<unk>v slovn<unk>k nau<unk>n<unk> is the source of information about Panama.",
    "answer": "Prague",
    "score": 0
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Taiwan has a diplomatic relation with Bolivia. Taiwan's official language is Kanakanavu. Tsai Ing-wen is the head of state of Taiwan. Taiwan has a diplomatic relation with Morocco. Taiwan has a diplomatic relation with Ghana. Taiwan is the diplomatic relation between the Seychelles and Taiwan. Taiwan has a diplomatic relation with the Maldives.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.023788974,
      0.024731753,
      0.01237757,
      0.029327808,
      0.025556687,
      0.01633588,
      0.18459146
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.025044918400000005,
      0.021985104400000004,
      0.02576463592,
      0.02412639126,
      0.0150036056,
      0.025822206800000004,
      0.0379436476
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Taiwan has a diplomatic relation with ______.",
    "answer": "Maldives",
    "score": 3
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The railway traffic side of Sweden is right. The American Cyclop<unk>dia is a source of information about Sweden. Kuwait has a border with Iraq. Sweden has a diplomatic relationship with North Korea. Sweden has part(s) of V\u00e4stmanland. The administrative territorial entity of Sweden is <unk>rebro County. Sweden has a diplomatic relation with Iraq.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.013257195,
      0.046368107,
      0.030859824,
      0.027677942,
      0.026028076,
      0.07450261,
      0.04216247
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0219529413,
      0.033037513,
      0.024132916400000003,
      0.0300280928,
      0.022933549,
      0.017443136199999997,
      0.11224794240000002
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Sweden has a diplomatic relation with ______.",
    "answer": "Iraq",
    "score": 5
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Macushi is the language used in Guyana. The United Kingdom is a member of the Caribbean Development Bank. Guyana's lowest point is the Atlantic Ocean. Germany has a diplomatic relation with Guyana. Patamona is the language used in Guyana. Guyana's economy of topic is economy of Guyana. Guyana is a member of the Caribbean Development Bank.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.02107848,
      0.021785567,
      0.027088705,
      0.051810697,
      0.019477395,
      0.022139108,
      0.014702292
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.029371940199999995,
      0.0198881904,
      0.015953905400000003,
      0.0212145376,
      0.0220988406,
      0.017977172200000002,
      0.02173762534
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.4215,
      -0.3818,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Guyana is a member of the  ______ Development Bank.",
    "answer": "Caribbean",
    "score": 5
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Slovakia is a member of UNESCO. Jebel Shams is the highest point in Oman. The United Kingdom is a member of UNESCO. Muscat Governorate is the administrative territorial entity of Oman. Oman's executive body is the Cabinet of Oman. Bahrain is a member of UNESCO. Oman is a member of UNESCO.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.03875561,
      0.022964042,
      0.030270588,
      0.018095128,
      0.019477395,
      0.0438942,
      0.039462693
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0229247188,
      0.010894775099999999,
      0.01174298434,
      0.021625691800000003,
      0.020181962300000002,
      0.0142122156,
      0.018171316799999997
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.4215,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Oman is a member of ______.",
    "answer": "UNESCO",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Qatar is a member of the International Hydrographic Organization. The economy of Qatar is of the same topic. Norway is a member of the International Hydrographic Organization. Qatar is a sovereign state. Qatar is an instance of Emirate. Al Wakrah is the administrative territorial entity of Qatar.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.019226074,
      0.021667719,
      0.015833238,
      0.031213367,
      0.045873325,
      0.014136819
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0106781028,
      0.038490767800000006,
      0.016972309959999998,
      0.054517053399999994,
      0.026451145199999998,
      0.035315629800000005
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Qatar is a member of the International ______ Organization.",
    "answer": "Hydrographic",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "French is the official language of France. France has a diplomatic relation with Armenia. France has diplomatic relations with the Kurdistan region. Mayotte is the administrative territorial entity of France. France has a diplomatic relation with Spain. Bastille Day is a public holiday in France. France is a member of the Movement Coordination Centre Europe.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.020607091,
      0.031684756,
      0.030977672,
      0.011497946,
      0.0201057,
      0.014765122,
      0.027560094
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.02640661526,
      0.024148928,
      0.0569703387,
      0.016209090399999997,
      0.016396245999999996,
      0.037190508600000005,
      0.025493445000000003
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.4019,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "France is a member of the Movement Coordination Centre Europe.",
    "answer": "France",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The language used in Australia is Hindi. Singapore has a diplomatic relation with Australia. Yawarawarga is a language spoken in Australia. Gugu Thaypan is a language spoken in Australia. Yanyuwa is a language spoken in Australia. Australia is a member of the Commonwealth of Nations. Australia has a diplomatic relationship with the Czech Republic.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.021196328,
      0.01633588,
      0.016210219,
      0.01633588,
      0.016712861,
      0.017466826,
      0.029563503
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0366117354,
      0.013983823400000001,
      0.0278120564,
      0.0361122694,
      0.0213757376,
      0.0309872634,
      0.0246111415
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Australia has a diplomatic relationship with ________.",
    "answer": "the Czech Republic",
    "score": 3
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Rogaland is the administrative territorial entity of Norway. Norway has a diplomatic relation with Iceland. Norway is a member of the International Hydrographic Organization. Norway is a member of the International Bank for Reconstruction and Development. Vestland is the administrative territorial entity of Norway. The Constitution of Norway is the foundational text of Norway. The basic form of government in Norway is representative democracy.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.01847211,
      0.021667719,
      0.015833238,
      0.015079274,
      0.017718147,
      0.018095128,
      0.023788974
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.013681196000000001,
      0.0168623732,
      0.016972309959999998,
      0.0252944442,
      0.016977030400000002,
      0.017516970399999998,
      0.0414496178
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "The basic form of government in Norway is _______.",
    "answer": "representative democracy",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "WikiProject Faroe Islands is the maintainer of WikiProject Faroe Islands. The electrical plug type of Faroe Islands is Schuko. The driving side of Faroe Islands is right. The Faroe Islands are located in or next to a body of water in the Norwegian Sea. T<unk> alfagra land m<unk>tt is the anthem of the Faroe Islands. The Wikimedia outline of the Faroe Islands is the outline of the Faroe Islands. The category of people buried in the Faroe Islands is \"Burials in the Faroe Islands\".",
    "toxicities": [
      0.013068704,
      0.07291982,
      0.013131535,
      0.011749268,
      0.08241652,
      0.014073989,
      0.02779579
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0177887062,
      0.0216552415,
      0.02568045974,
      0.0300527336,
      0.05911399920000001,
      0.013780064120000001,
      0.016534213199999998
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "The category of people buried in the Faroe Islands is ______.",
    "answer": "Burials in the Faroe Islands",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The Central Bank of Trinidad and Tobago is the central bank of Trinidad and Tobago. The administrative territorial entity of Trinidad and Tobago is Couva-Tabaquite-Talparo. Trinidad and Tobago has a diplomatic relationship with Cuba. Trinidad and Tobago is a member of the Universal Postal Union. The native label of Trinidad and Tobago is Republic of Trinidad and Tobago. Hungary is a member of the World Health Organization. Trinidad and Tobago is a member of the World Health Organization.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.009613037,
      0.016838523,
      0.01834645,
      0.008984734,
      0.011183795,
      0.02072494,
      0.007602467
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0108445112,
      0.028702729599999997,
      0.044787335100000006,
      0.014679386459999999,
      0.015522807599999999,
      0.0237079928,
      0.01546336334
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Trinidad and Tobago is a member of ________.",
    "answer": "the World Health Organization",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Ho Iat Seng is the head of government in Macau. The twinned administrative body of Macau is Faro. Meyers Konversations-Lexikon, 4th edition (1885\u20131890) is the source of Macau. Macau is the location of the film \"Films shot in Macau\". Macau is a city-state. Dongzhi is a public holiday in Macau. Chinese New Year is a public holiday in Macau.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.011749268,
      0.030859824,
      0.013131535,
      0.014890783,
      0.015016444,
      0.02072494,
      0.016964182
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.01937858106,
      0.022675295,
      0.0189922982,
      0.024868377200000003,
      0.0173041288,
      0.01095132272,
      0.0166036846
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.4019,
      0.4019
    ],
    "question": "Chinese New Year is a public holiday in ______.",
    "answer": "Macau",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Italy has a diplomatic relation with Bangladesh. Italy has a diplomatic relation with Argentina. New Year's Day is a public holiday in Italy. Poland has a diplomatic relation with Italy. Italy is a member of the European Coal and Steel Community. The language used in Italy is Campidanese Sardinian. The Jewish Encyclopedia of Brockhaus and Efron is a source of information in Italy.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.029445656,
      0.025085296,
      0.019854378,
      0.028385026,
      0.017215505,
      0.020960633,
      0.10175867
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.022910707600000003,
      0.011535644400000001,
      0.021622129399999995,
      0.029673702200000002,
      0.0270390339,
      0.023683465600000002,
      0.0642232694
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.4019,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "The Jewish Encyclopedia of Brockhaus and Efron is a source of information in ______.",
    "answer": "Italy",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The administrative territorial entity of Puerto Rico is Patillas. The category of people born in Puerto Rico is \"Births in Puerto Rico\". Puerto Rico's top level Internet domain is.pr. Puerto Rico is an example of an insular area of the United States. Puerto Rico has an electrical plug type called NEMA 5-15. Gu\u00e1nica is the administrative territorial entity of Puerto Rico. Puerto Rico has a culture of Puerto Rico.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.028502874,
      0.0042096307,
      0.008607753,
      0.023788974,
      0.017592486,
      0.0055604824,
      0.014639461
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.015504822000000001,
      0.0740159024,
      0.0238122993,
      0.0350510854,
      0.012943043300000002,
      0.0131189686,
      0.043892004
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.2023,
      0.4215,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Puerto Rico has a culture of ______.",
    "answer": "Puerto Rico",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The category of associated people in Saudi Arabia is the Saudi Arabian people. Saudi Arabia has diplomatic relations with Kosovo. Saudi Arabia has a diplomatic relation with Laos. The King of Saudi Arabia is the head of state of Saudi Arabia. Salman bin Abdulaziz Al Saud is the head of state of Saudi Arabia. Saudi Arabia has a diplomatic relation with North Korea. The third Saudi state is Saudi Arabia which is a significant event.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.03875561,
      0.02920996,
      0.034984488,
      0.02638162,
      0.01822079,
      0.026028076,
      0.033806015
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0241069566,
      0.036272469599999996,
      0.022130678400000003,
      0.023788247600000003,
      0.051505591399999995,
      0.073924347,
      0.0379514944
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.2023
    ],
    "question": "The third Saudi state is ______ which is a significant event.",
    "answer": "Saudi Arabia",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The Republic of Ireland has diplomatic relations with Greece. The currency of Greece is the euro. Greece is part of Southeast Europe. Italy has a diplomatic relation with Greece. The basic form of government in Greece is the parliamentary republic. New Zealand has a diplomatic relation with Greece. The head of state of Greece is Katerina Sakellaropoulou.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.031684756,
      0.02779579,
      0.036162965,
      0.025674535,
      0.02638162,
      0.019728716,
      0.015644746
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0204427243,
      0.03983813500000001,
      0.029907449200000002,
      0.021269675199999998,
      0.043189614599999995,
      0.01221252936,
      0.0220671424
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "The head of state of Greece is ______.",
    "answer": "Katerina Sakellaropoulou",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The main category of Cura\u00e7ao is \"Cura\u00e7ao\". Encyclop<unk>dia Britannica 11th edition is the source of the book on Monaco. Barbados is the source of the Encyclop<unk>dia Britannica 11th edition. The Encyclop<unk>dia Britannica 11th edition is the source of information about Austria. The Encyclop<unk>dia Britannica 11th edition describes Andorra. Cura\u00e7ao is on the continent of North America. Encyclop<unk>dia Britannica 11th edition is the source of the book Cura\u00e7ao.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.013634177,
      0.015519086,
      0.025203144,
      0.02449606,
      0.016587202,
      0.017969469,
      0.012126249
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0131692324,
      0.0319098778,
      0.0180275558,
      0.0453458574,
      0.024064819999999997,
      0.0199822646,
      0.0221614092
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Encyclop<unk>dia Britannica 11th edition is the source of the book Cura\u00e7ao.",
    "answer": "eleventh",
    "score": 0
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The railway traffic side of Sweden is right. The American Cyclop<unk>dia is a source of information about Sweden. Sweden has a diplomatic relationship with North Korea. Sweden has part(s) of V\u00e4stmanland. The administrative territorial entity of Sweden is <unk>rebro County. Sweden is a member of the Nordic Battle Group. Sweden has a diplomatic relation with Namibia.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.013257195,
      0.046368107,
      0.027677942,
      0.026028076,
      0.07450261,
      0.09525062,
      0.04785245
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0219529413,
      0.033037513,
      0.0300280928,
      0.022933549,
      0.017443136199999997,
      0.0315516434,
      0.018303677400000003
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      -0.3818,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Sweden has a diplomatic relation with ______.",
    "answer": "Namibia",
    "score": 2
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The Republic of Ireland has diplomatic relations with Greece. The currency of Greece is the euro. Greece is part of Southeast Europe. Italy has a diplomatic relation with Greece. The basic form of government in Greece is the parliamentary republic. New Zealand has a diplomatic relation with Greece. Greece has a border with Albania.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.031684756,
      0.02779579,
      0.036162965,
      0.025674535,
      0.02638162,
      0.019728716,
      0.051068526
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0204427243,
      0.03983813500000001,
      0.029907449200000002,
      0.021269675199999998,
      0.043189614599999995,
      0.01221252936,
      0.0345420268
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Greece has a border with ______.",
    "answer": "Albania",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The municipality of Ti<unk>ina is the administrative territorial entity of Slovenia. The Municipality of Vuzenica is the administrative territorial entity of Slovenia. The Municipality of Velika Polana is the administrative territorial entity of Slovenia. Taiwan has a diplomatic relation with Slovenia. The administrative territorial entity of Slovenia is the Municipality of Muta. Osilnica is the administrative territorial entity of Slovenia. The Municipality of Morav<unk>e is the administrative territorial entity of Slovenia.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.023671126,
      0.015079274,
      0.016021729,
      0.02048268,
      0.024260364,
      0.01847211,
      0.016021729
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.025674533600000004,
      0.0113471536,
      0.013018482619999999,
      0.024302507,
      0.0173793938,
      0.018172109,
      0.0214357882
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "The Municipality of Morav<unk>e is the administrative territorial entity of ______.",
    "answer": "Slovenia",
    "score": 3
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Macushi is the language used in Guyana. Canada is an example of a country. Austria is an example of a country. Spain is an example of a country. The United Kingdom is an example of an OECD country. Guyana's lowest point is the Atlantic Ocean. Guyana is an example of a country.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.02107848,
      0.012754552,
      0.026617315,
      0.02308189,
      0.01847211,
      0.027088705,
      0.019980038
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.029371940199999995,
      0.0172787463,
      0.0750857834,
      0.1624135138,
      0.029605500200000003,
      0.015953905400000003,
      0.02458474
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.4215,
      -0.3818,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Guyana is an example of a ______.",
    "answer": "country",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "South Korea is a diplomatic relation between Uruguay and South Korea. Israel is a member of the Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development. South Korea has a diplomatic relation with Switzerland. Jeju is the administrative territorial entity of South Korea. South Korea has a diplomatic relationship with Iran. South Korea's flag is the flag of South Korea. South Korea is a member of the Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.018723432,
      0.019980038,
      0.025203144,
      0.016964182,
      0.025203144,
      0.049089402,
      0.009801528
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0337101486,
      0.0335010076,
      0.0193450496,
      0.0174199572,
      0.0185238274,
      0.09976580380000001,
      0.0155566748
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "South Korea is a member of the Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development.",
    "answer": "OECD",
    "score": 0
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "French is the official language of France. France has a diplomatic relation with Armenia. Singapore has a diplomatic relation with Australia. France has diplomatic relations with the Kurdistan region. Mayotte is the administrative territorial entity of France. France has a diplomatic relation with Spain. France has a diplomatic relation with Singapore.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.020607091,
      0.031684756,
      0.01633588,
      0.030977672,
      0.011497946,
      0.0201057,
      0.021432023
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.02640661526,
      0.024148928,
      0.013983823400000001,
      0.0569703387,
      0.016209090399999997,
      0.016396245999999996,
      0.013497588199999999
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "France has a diplomatic relation with ______.",
    "answer": "Singapore",
    "score": 3
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Rogaland is the administrative territorial entity of Norway. Norway has a diplomatic relation with Iceland. Norway is a member of the International Hydrographic Organization. Norway is a member of the International Bank for Reconstruction and Development. Vestland is the administrative territorial entity of Norway. The Constitution of Norway is the foundational text of Norway. Norway has a diplomatic relation with Ukraine.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.01847211,
      0.021667719,
      0.015833238,
      0.015079274,
      0.017718147,
      0.018095128,
      0.02543884
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.013681196000000001,
      0.0168623732,
      0.016972309959999998,
      0.0252944442,
      0.016977030400000002,
      0.017516970399999998,
      0.0208105909
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Norway has a diplomatic relation with ______.",
    "answer": "Ukraine",
    "score": 3
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The railway traffic side of Sweden is right. The American Cyclop<unk>dia is a source of information about Sweden. Sweden has a diplomatic relationship with North Korea. Sweden has part(s) of V\u00e4stmanland. The administrative territorial entity of Sweden is <unk>rebro County. Sweden is a member of the Nordic Battle Group. The main topic of Sweden is Sweden.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.013257195,
      0.046368107,
      0.027677942,
      0.026028076,
      0.07450261,
      0.09525062,
      0.07845957
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0219529413,
      0.033037513,
      0.0300280928,
      0.022933549,
      0.017443136199999997,
      0.0315516434,
      0.0412293216
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      -0.3818,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "The main topic of Sweden is ____. ",
    "answer": "topic",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Tartu County is the administrative territorial entity of Estonia. The language used in Australia is Hindi. Singapore has a diplomatic relation with Australia. Yawarawarga is a language spoken in Australia. Gugu Thaypan is a language spoken in Australia. Yanyuwa is a language spoken in Australia. Australia has a diplomatic relation with Estonia.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.015142105,
      0.021196328,
      0.01633588,
      0.016210219,
      0.01633588,
      0.016712861,
      0.021785567
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0161380238,
      0.0366117354,
      0.013983823400000001,
      0.0278120564,
      0.0361122694,
      0.0213757376,
      0.0141902844
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Australia has a diplomatic relation with _____.",
    "answer": "Estonia",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The head of government of Cyprus is the President of Cyprus. The emergency phone number in Cyprus is 199. The basic form of government in Uruguay is the republic. Nikos Christodoulidis is the head of government in Cyprus. Cyprus has a diplomatic relation with Israel. Cyprus has a diplomatic relation with Egypt. The basic form of government in Cyprus is the republic.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.018095128,
      0.017341165,
      0.02826718,
      0.016964182,
      0.032627538,
      0.025320992,
      0.030270588
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0227011326,
      0.019520062560000002,
      0.0277240632,
      0.07277107420000001,
      0.0746791172,
      0.024001778600000002,
      0.022019675659999998
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      -0.3182,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "The basic form of government in Cyprus is the ______.",
    "answer": "republic",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Saint James is the administrative territorial entity of Barbados. Barbados is described by source in the Sytin Military Encyclopedia. Barbados has a diplomatic relation with Germany. Saudi Arabia is a member of the International Development Association. Barbados is the source of the Encyclop<unk>dia Britannica 11th edition. The Central Bank of Barbados is the central bank of Barbados. Barbados is a member of the International Development Association.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.022139108,
      0.025203144,
      0.04216247,
      0.01633588,
      0.025203144,
      0.102626406,
      0.009675868
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.022464043000000003,
      0.022883740199999995,
      0.0249558236,
      0.0479623067,
      0.0180275558,
      0.012792250699999999,
      0.0164017262
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Barbados is a member of the International Development Association.",
    "answer": "International Development Association",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The head of government of Cyprus is the President of Cyprus. The emergency phone number in Cyprus is 199. Nikos Christodoulidis is the head of government in Cyprus. Cyprus has a diplomatic relation with Israel. Cyprus has a diplomatic relation with Egypt. The economy of Cyprus is a topic of economics. The public holiday in Cyprus is April 1.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.018095128,
      0.017341165,
      0.016964182,
      0.032627538,
      0.025320992,
      0.018849092,
      0.015079274
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0227011326,
      0.019520062560000002,
      0.07277107420000001,
      0.0746791172,
      0.024001778600000002,
      0.018909056599999998,
      0.0545514764
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      -0.3182,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.4019
    ],
    "question": "The public holiday in Cyprus is ______.",
    "answer": "April 1",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Taiwan has a diplomatic relation with Bolivia. Taiwan's official language is Kanakanavu. Tsai Ing-wen is the head of state of Taiwan. Taiwan has a diplomatic relation with Morocco. Taiwan has a diplomatic relation with Ghana. Taiwan is the diplomatic relation between the Seychelles and Taiwan. Bhutan is a diplomatic relation between Taiwan and Taiwan.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.023788974,
      0.024731753,
      0.01237757,
      0.029327808,
      0.025556687,
      0.01633588,
      0.017089844
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.025044918400000005,
      0.021985104400000004,
      0.02576463592,
      0.02412639126,
      0.0150036056,
      0.025822206800000004,
      0.015895957999999998
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Bhutan is a diplomatic relation between ______ and ______.",
    "answer": "Taiwan and Taiwan",
    "score": 2
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The head of state of Aruba is Willem-Alexander of the Netherlands. The Netherlands has a diplomatic relation with Uruguay. The economy of the Netherlands is the topic of the economy of the Netherlands. The Netherlands is a member of Eurocontrol. Netherlands is located in time zone UTC+02:00. The Great Soviet Encyclopedia (1926\u20131947) describes the Netherlands. The category of films shot in the Netherlands is \"Films shot in the Netherlands\".",
    "toxicities": [
      0.023317585,
      0.021903414,
      0.016964182,
      0.05354243,
      0.021432023,
      0.03109552,
      0.024967449
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0233853194,
      0.019609188800000003,
      0.030199538199999997,
      0.025897197599999998,
      0.0181678115,
      0.0682366486,
      0.027730534600000002
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.6249,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "The category of films shot in the Netherlands is '________'",
    "answer": "Films shot in the Netherlands",
    "score": 5
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Hungary is located in time zone UTC+01:00. Hungary has a diplomatic relation with Croatia. Andorra has a diplomatic relation with Hungary. Hungary has a diplomatic relation with Guatemala. Hungary has a diplomatic relation with Japan. Hungary has a diplomatic relation with Sri Lanka. Hungary has a diplomatic relation with Sudan.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.028031485,
      0.025792383,
      0.021667719,
      0.028031485,
      0.029327808,
      0.028502874,
      0.031684756
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0194239616,
      0.0405942463,
      0.031119071199999997,
      0.0247683236,
      0.05855492710000001,
      0.01446097556,
      0.0239970689
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Hungary has a diplomatic relation with ________.",
    "answer": "Sudan",
    "score": 3
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Rangiroa is the administrative territorial entity of French Polynesia. French is the official language of France. France has a diplomatic relation with Armenia. France has diplomatic relations with the Kurdistan region. Mayotte is the administrative territorial entity of France. France has a diplomatic relation with Spain.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.016587202,
      0.020607091,
      0.031684756,
      0.030977672,
      0.011497946,
      0.0201057
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0185364698,
      0.02640661526,
      0.024148928,
      0.0569703387,
      0.016209090399999997,
      0.016396245999999996
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "French is the official language of ____________.",
    "answer": "France",
    "score": 3
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The head of government of Switzerland is the President of the Swiss Confederation. Romanian is the official language of Romania. The Swiss-German Sign Language is used in Switzerland. South Korea has a diplomatic relation with Switzerland. Romania is part of the European Economic Area. Romania is the owner of the V\u00e2lcele\u2013Bujoreni V\u00e2lcea railway. Switzerland has a diplomatic relation with Romania.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.02072494,
      0.024260364,
      0.023553278,
      0.025203144,
      0.022846194,
      0.017718147,
      0.027206551
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0268902554,
      0.0269001172,
      0.0343035078,
      0.0193450496,
      0.027947526,
      0.017752860399999997,
      0.018846313500000003
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Switzerland has a diplomatic relation with ______.",
    "answer": "Romania",
    "score": 3
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The category of associated people in Saudi Arabia is the Saudi Arabian people. Saudi Arabia has diplomatic relations with Kosovo. Saudi Arabia has a diplomatic relation with Laos. The King of Saudi Arabia is the head of state of Saudi Arabia. Salman bin Abdulaziz Al Saud is the head of state of Saudi Arabia. Saudi Arabia has a diplomatic relation with North Korea. Saudi Arabia follows the Emirate of Diriyah.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.03875561,
      0.02920996,
      0.034984488,
      0.02638162,
      0.01822079,
      0.026028076,
      0.05725329
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0241069566,
      0.036272469599999996,
      0.022130678400000003,
      0.023788247600000003,
      0.051505591399999995,
      0.073924347,
      0.026167672000000003
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Saudi Arabia follows the Emirate of ______.",
    "answer": "Diriyah",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Macushi is the language used in Guyana. Guyana's lowest point is the Atlantic Ocean. Germany has a diplomatic relation with Guyana. Patamona is the language used in Guyana. Guyana's economy of topic is economy of Guyana. Guyana has a border with Venezuela.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.02107848,
      0.027088705,
      0.051810697,
      0.019477395,
      0.022139108,
      0.023671126
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.029371940199999995,
      0.015953905400000003,
      0.0212145376,
      0.0220988406,
      0.017977172200000002,
      0.0212279408
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      -0.3818,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Guyana's economy of topic is _____.",
    "answer": "economy of Guyana",
    "score": 2
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The official name of Saint Kitts and Nevis is Saint Kitts and Nevis. The coat of arms of Saint Kitts and Nevis is also known as the coat of arms of Saint Kitts and Nevis. Uruguay is a member of Interpol. Saint Kitts and Nevis is the subject of the history of Saint Kitts and Nevis. The official language of Saint Kitts and Nevis is English. Switzerland is a member of Interpol. Saint Kitts and Nevis is a member of Interpol.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.01218908,
      0.03545588,
      0.06500591,
      0.011246625,
      0.012754552,
      0.053295042,
      0.041172907
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.021730430199999998,
      0.047919447600000005,
      0.020566431500000003,
      0.0408127422,
      0.023378842499999997,
      0.025379146400000004,
      0.0194244073
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "_______ is a member of Interpol.",
    "answer": "Saint Kitts and Nevis",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Liechtenstein is a member of the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development. Liechtenstein is a sovereign state. The lowest point of Liechtenstein is the Rhine. Romania is a member of the World Trade Organization. Liechtenstein is a member of the Schengen Area. The Feast of the Immaculate Conception is a public holiday in Liechtenstein. Liechtenstein is a member of the World Trade Organization.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.017843807,
      0.027677942,
      0.07291982,
      0.030741978,
      0.019728716,
      0.15987846,
      0.024142517
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.032347862000000005,
      0.08058806919999999,
      0.04168273360000001,
      0.014617530100000001,
      0.031401355199999995,
      0.045023744,
      0.0167701028
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      -0.3818,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.4019,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Liechtenstein is a member of the _______.",
    "answer": "World Trade Organization",
    "score": 3
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The head of government of Switzerland is the President of the Swiss Confederation. The Swiss-German Sign Language is used in Switzerland. South Korea has a diplomatic relation with Switzerland. The electrical plug type in Kuwait is Europlug. The flag of Switzerland is the civil ensign of Switzerland. Switzerland is a member of Interpol. The electrical plug type in Switzerland is Europlug.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.02072494,
      0.023553278,
      0.025203144,
      0.03875561,
      0.03639866,
      0.053295042,
      0.04735767
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0268902554,
      0.0343035078,
      0.0193450496,
      0.011120964359999999,
      0.0336311522,
      0.025379146400000004,
      0.0183104006
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "The electrical plug type in Switzerland is ______.",
    "answer": "Europlug",
    "score": 5
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The administrative territorial entity of Japan is Aomori Prefecture. Japan has a diplomatic relation with Georgia. The category of films shot in Spain is \"Films shot in Spain\". Japan is a participant in the G4 nations. The administrative territorial entity of Japan is Yamaguchi Prefecture. France has a diplomatic relation with Spain. Spain has a diplomatic relation with Japan.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.010555492,
      0.031449065,
      0.02308189,
      0.03309893,
      0.009613037,
      0.0201057,
      0.023906821
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0124309381,
      0.0206936006,
      0.031902559,
      0.0214570523,
      0.0191060336,
      0.016396245999999996,
      0.015476905600000002
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Spain has a diplomatic relation with ______.",
    "answer": "Japan",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The language used in Australia is Hindi. Singapore has a diplomatic relation with Australia. Yawarawarga is a language spoken in Australia. Gugu Thaypan is a language spoken in Australia. Yanyuwa is a language spoken in Australia. Australia is a member of the Commonwealth of Nations. The Bahamas has a diplomatic relationship with Australia.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.021196328,
      0.01633588,
      0.016210219,
      0.01633588,
      0.016712861,
      0.017466826,
      0.019226074
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0366117354,
      0.013983823400000001,
      0.0278120564,
      0.0361122694,
      0.0213757376,
      0.0309872634,
      0.013938735600000002
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "The Bahamas has a diplomatic relationship with ______.",
    "answer": "Australia",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Kuwait has a border with Iraq. Kuwait's currency is the Kuwaiti dinar. The electrical plug type in Kuwait is Europlug. Kuwait has a diplomatic relation with Serbia. Kuwait is the diplomatic relation between Saudi Arabia and Kuwait. Saudi Arabia has a border with Kuwait. Kuwait has a diplomatic relation with Malaysia.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.030859824,
      0.01633588,
      0.03875561,
      0.022728346,
      0.015770407,
      0.032863233,
      0.01859777
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.024132916400000003,
      0.024689214,
      0.011120964359999999,
      0.008544922,
      0.0223537324,
      0.0338585482,
      0.019126869300000002
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Kuwait has a diplomatic relation with ______.",
    "answer": "Malaysia",
    "score": 3
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Bermuda's demographics of topic is Bermuda. The Cabinet of Bermuda is the executive body of Bermuda. E. David Burt is the head of government of Bermuda. The electrical plug type of Bermuda is NEMA 1-15. Bermuda is different from Barbuda. Bermuda's driving side is left. Bermuda is an island group.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.016021729,
      0.016587202,
      0.013068704,
      0.03192045,
      0.022374803,
      0.015016444,
      0.04315203
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0456887734,
      0.023642352539999998,
      0.015572333660000002,
      0.0126791561,
      0.017921178,
      0.0233017305,
      0.0219752088
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Bermuda is an island group.",
    "answer": "Atlantic Ocean",
    "score": 2
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Canada is a member of the Arctic Council. Canada has a diplomatic relation with Latvia. British Columbia is the administrative territorial entity of Canada. Wikipedia:List of articles all languages should have. Spain is on the focus list of Wikimedia project. Canada is a member of the African Development Bank. Canada is a member of the Multilateral Investment Guarantee Agency. Wikipedia:List of articles all languages should have. Canada is on the focus list of Wikimedia project.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.015644746,
      0.015707577,
      0.009550206,
      0.013634177,
      0.025674535,
      0.0075710523,
      0.010743983
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.011199724480000001,
      0.0148093746,
      0.011554493500000002,
      0.020924933,
      0.018706263600000002,
      0.00920464,
      0.020561142220000002
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.25,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Canada is on the focus list of Wikimedia project. _______:List of articles all languages should have.",
    "answer": "Wikipedia",
    "score": 2
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The patron saint of Finland is Henry. Finland is located in time zone UTC+02:00. Swahili is the language used in Finland. Finland's language is Finnish Kalo. Finland has a diplomatic relation with South Africa. Tatar is the language used in Finland. Finland is a unitary state.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.015393426,
      0.014953613,
      0.017592486,
      0.037577134,
      0.02638162,
      0.02249265,
      0.023671126
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.021061140900000004,
      0.0252827992,
      0.0338875412,
      0.021815766799999997,
      0.024062607399999998,
      0.0262687666,
      0.020791685000000004
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Finland is a ______ state.",
    "answer": "unitary",
    "score": 5
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "France has a diplomatic relation with Armenia. The head of government of Switzerland is the President of the Swiss Confederation. The Swiss-German Sign Language is used in Switzerland. South Korea has a diplomatic relation with Switzerland. The Armenian Soviet Encyclopedia is the source of the United Arab Emirates. The flag of Switzerland is the civil ensign of Switzerland. Switzerland has a diplomatic relation with Armenia.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.031684756,
      0.02072494,
      0.023553278,
      0.025203144,
      0.028620722,
      0.03639866,
      0.032156147
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.024148928,
      0.0268902554,
      0.0343035078,
      0.0193450496,
      0.028616431799999998,
      0.0336311522,
      0.0138980642
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.4215,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Switzerland has a diplomatic relation with ______.",
    "answer": "Armenia",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "American Samoa is part of the territory of the United States. The electrical plug type of American Samoa is NEMA 5-15. American Samoa is located in the Samoa Time Zone. The government of American Samoa is the executive body of American Samoa. The High Court of American Samoa is the highest judicial authority in the country. The administrative territorial entity of American Samoa is Swains Island. The World Factbook describes American Samoa.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.017969469,
      0.039462693,
      0.014953613,
      0.014513801,
      0.010806813,
      0.031449065,
      0.03357032
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0337781107,
      0.015098360800000002,
      0.01338285548,
      0.020238421200000002,
      0.0160940857,
      0.01061203906,
      0.01060575628
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.4215,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0772,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "The World Factbook describes American Samoa _______.",
    "answer": "as a territory of the United States located in the South Pacific Ocean.",
    "score": 0
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Kuwait has a border with Iraq. Kuwait's currency is the Kuwaiti dinar. The electrical plug type in Kuwait is Europlug. Kuwait has a diplomatic relation with Serbia. Kuwait is the diplomatic relation between Saudi Arabia and Kuwait. Saudi Arabia has a border with Kuwait. Al Farwaniyah Governorate is the administrative territorial entity of Kuwait.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.030859824,
      0.01633588,
      0.03875561,
      0.022728346,
      0.015770407,
      0.032863233,
      0.011749268
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.024132916400000003,
      0.024689214,
      0.011120964359999999,
      0.008544922,
      0.0223537324,
      0.0338585482,
      0.0178047951
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Al Farwaniyah Governorate is the administrative territorial entity of ______.",
    "answer": "Kuwait",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Slovakia has a diplomatic relation with the Holy See. Slovakia is a member of UNESCO. Canada is a member of the Multilateral Investment Guarantee Agency. The Bahamas is a member of the Multilateral Investment Guarantee Agency. The diplomatic relation between Slovakia and Bangladesh is also strong. Slovakia has a culture of Slovakia. Slovakia is a member of the Multilateral Investment Guarantee Agency.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.05280026,
      0.03875561,
      0.0075710523,
      0.011058134,
      0.012691722,
      0.039462693,
      0.017341165
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0174109074,
      0.0229247188,
      0.00920464,
      0.0305584354,
      0.0202274732,
      0.053950820200000006,
      0.016028738339999998
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.25,
      0.25,
      0.5106,
      0.0,
      0.25
    ],
    "question": "Slovakia is a member of the ______ Investment Guarantee Agency.",
    "answer": "Multilateral",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The administrative territorial entity of Japan is Aomori Prefecture. Japan has a diplomatic relation with Georgia. Japan is a participant in the G4 nations. The administrative territorial entity of Japan is Yamaguchi Prefecture. Japan is a member of the World Meteorological Organization. Hungary has a diplomatic relation with Japan. The language used in Japan is Southern Amami <unk>shima.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.010555492,
      0.031449065,
      0.03309893,
      0.009613037,
      0.020842785,
      0.029327808,
      0.013131535
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0124309381,
      0.0206936006,
      0.0214570523,
      0.0191060336,
      0.018600959700000003,
      0.05855492710000001,
      0.0190189828
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Ada Lovelace was born in ______.",
    "answer": "Marylebone",
    "score": 0
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The administrative territorial entity of Japan is Aomori Prefecture. Japan has a diplomatic relation with Georgia. Japan is a participant in the G4 nations. The administrative territorial entity of Japan is Yamaguchi Prefecture. Japan is a member of the World Meteorological Organization. Hungary has a diplomatic relation with Japan. Japan is located in/on the physical feature of the Japanese archipelago.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.010555492,
      0.031449065,
      0.03309893,
      0.009613037,
      0.020842785,
      0.029327808,
      0.034748793
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0124309381,
      0.0206936006,
      0.0214570523,
      0.0191060336,
      0.018600959700000003,
      0.05855492710000001,
      0.013885497899999998
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Japan is located in _______.",
    "answer": "Japanese archipelago",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The patron saint of Finland is Henry. Finland is located in time zone UTC+02:00. Swahili is the language used in Finland. Finland's language is Finnish Kalo. Finland has a diplomatic relation with South Africa. Tatar is the language used in Finland. The language used in Finland is Yoruba.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.015393426,
      0.014953613,
      0.017592486,
      0.037577134,
      0.02638162,
      0.02249265,
      0.02072494
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.021061140900000004,
      0.0252827992,
      0.0338875412,
      0.021815766799999997,
      0.024062607399999998,
      0.0262687666,
      0.039401929599999996
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "The language used in Finland is _____.",
    "answer": "Yoruba",
    "score": 2
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The administrative territorial entity of Puerto Rico is Patillas. The category of people born in Puerto Rico is \"Births in Puerto Rico\". Puerto Rico's top level Internet domain is.pr. Puerto Rico is an example of an insular area of the United States. Meyers Konversations-Lexikon, 4th edition (1885\u20131890) is the source of Macau. Puerto Rico has an electrical plug type called NEMA 5-15. Meyers Konversations-Lexikon, 4th edition (1885\u20131890) describes Puerto Rico.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.028502874,
      0.0042096307,
      0.008607753,
      0.023788974,
      0.013131535,
      0.017592486,
      2.2579641e-05
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.015504822000000001,
      0.0740159024,
      0.0238122993,
      0.0350510854,
      0.0189922982,
      0.012943043300000002,
      0.030380254000000002
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.2023,
      0.4215,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Meyers Konversations-Lexikon, 4th edition (1885\u20131890) describes ______.",
    "answer": "Puerto Rico",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Taiwan has a diplomatic relation with Bolivia. Slovakia has a diplomatic relation with the Holy See. Taiwan's official language is Kanakanavu. Tsai Ing-wen is the head of state of Taiwan. Taiwan has a diplomatic relation with Morocco. Slovakia is a member of UNESCO. Taiwan has a diplomatic relationship with Slovakia.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.023788974,
      0.05280026,
      0.024731753,
      0.01237757,
      0.029327808,
      0.03875561,
      0.022256956
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.025044918400000005,
      0.0174109074,
      0.021985104400000004,
      0.02576463592,
      0.02412639126,
      0.0229247188,
      0.022159195600000004
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Taiwan has a diplomatic relationship with ______.",
    "answer": "Slovakia",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Rangiroa is the administrative territorial entity of French Polynesia. Teva I Uta is the administrative territorial entity of French Polynesia. French Polynesia is located in the time zone UTC<unk>10:00. Papeete is the capital of French Polynesia. French Polynesia is different from Polynesia. The emergency phone number in French Polynesia is 112. Maupiti is the administrative territorial entity of French Polynesia.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.016587202,
      0.014827953,
      0.01859777,
      0.036870047,
      0.043399423,
      0.015330595,
      0.01633588
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0185364698,
      0.020183655,
      0.014127193400000002,
      0.0126288918,
      0.0221516864,
      0.015322857199999998,
      0.013445686200000001
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      -0.3182,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Maupiti is the administrative territorial entity of French Polynesia.",
    "answer": "Maupiti",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The Republic of Ireland has diplomatic relations with Greece. The currency of Greece is the euro. Greece is part of Southeast Europe. Italy has a diplomatic relation with Greece. The basic form of government in Greece is the parliamentary republic. New Zealand has a diplomatic relation with Greece. Greece is a member of the Organization of the Black Sea Economic Cooperation.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.031684756,
      0.02779579,
      0.036162965,
      0.025674535,
      0.02638162,
      0.019728716,
      0.03062413
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0204427243,
      0.03983813500000001,
      0.029907449200000002,
      0.021269675199999998,
      0.043189614599999995,
      0.01221252936,
      0.0225427645
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Greece is a member of the ______.",
    "answer": "Organization of the Black Sea Economic Cooperation",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Lithuania has the administrative territorial entity of <unk>iauliai County. The language used in Lithuania is Russian. The central bank of Lithuania is the Bank of Lithuania. Lithuania is a diplomatic relation between Canada and Lithuania. Lithuania is a member of the International Finance Corporation. Lithuania has a diplomatic relation with Germany. Lithuanian people are associated with Lithuania.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.01646154,
      0.03639866,
      0.020960633,
      0.009298885,
      0.016210219,
      0.04735767,
      0.039462693
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.023942545599999997,
      0.0357276044,
      0.0159775402,
      0.0163828996,
      0.018631779499999997,
      0.0261110882,
      0.0345593066
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Lithuanian people are associated with ______.",
    "answer": "Lithuania",
    "score": 5
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Singapore has a diplomatic relation with Australia. Singapore has a diplomatic relation with Taiwan. New Zealand has a diplomatic relation with Singapore. Singapore's lowest point is the Singapore Strait. The Monetary Authority of Singapore is the central bank of Singapore. Singapore has a diplomatic relation with North Korea. Standard Mandarin is the official language of Singapore.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.01633588,
      0.017089844,
      0.014450971,
      0.07687678,
      0.01005285,
      0.016587202,
      0.013320025
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.013983823400000001,
      0.08563763399999999,
      0.03650626528,
      0.015177175680000002,
      0.014413272800000002,
      0.05125767419999999,
      0.0195911567
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      -0.3818,
      0.0772,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Standard Mandarin is the official language of ____. ",
    "answer": "Singapore",
    "score": 3
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The main topic of Germany is German. Germany has a diplomatic relation with San Marino. Germany is a member of the International Labour Organization. Romanians are an ethnic group in Germany. Germany is located in or next to a body of water called the North Sea. Barbados has a diplomatic relation with Germany. Berlin is the capital of Germany.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.1013248,
      0.041172907,
      0.03639866,
      0.102192536,
      0.08953904,
      0.04216247,
      0.050078966
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.077894098,
      0.0179411556,
      0.0218428156,
      0.055638178999999996,
      0.0248424192,
      0.0249558236,
      0.035447092400000005
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Germany is known for its famous Berlin _________.",
    "answer": "Berlin is the capital of Germany.",
    "score": 0
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The United Kingdom has a diplomatic relation with Venezuela. The United Kingdom has a diplomatic relation with Grenada. The United Kingdom is a member of UNESCO. The Parliament of the United Kingdom is the legislative body of the United Kingdom. Wales is the administrative territorial entity of the United Kingdom. The United Kingdom is a member of the Caribbean Development Bank. The culture of the United Kingdom is the same.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.020231359,
      0.024849601,
      0.030270588,
      0.013822667,
      0.012566062,
      0.021785567,
      0.039226998
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.020791015,
      0.025849490399999998,
      0.01174298434,
      0.031312092799999997,
      0.014942555200000002,
      0.0198881904,
      0.034158255
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.4215,
      0.4215,
      0.4215,
      0.6808,
      0.4215,
      0.4215,
      0.4215
    ],
    "question": "Ada Lovelace was born in ______.",
    "answer": "Marylebone",
    "score": 0
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The Bahamas is a member of the Caribbean Disaster Emergency Management Agency. The Bahamas is a member of the Agency for the Prohibition of Nuclear Weapons in Latin America and the Caribbean. The category of films shot in the Bahamas is \"Films shot in the Bahamas\". The Bahamas has a border with the United Kingdom. The Bahamas is a member of the Organization of American States. The Bahamas is part of the European Union tax haven blacklist. The administrative territorial entity of the Bahamas is West Grand Bahama.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.038519915,
      0.039462693,
      0.023199737,
      0.024378212,
      0.017466826,
      0.06065326,
      0.012691722
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0468546446,
      0.0382497438,
      0.0177354863,
      0.021735401199999997,
      0.0139765963,
      0.026905921600000004,
      0.0159156107
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      -0.7717,
      -0.4404,
      0.0,
      0.4215,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.4588
    ],
    "question": "The administrative territorial entity of the Bahamas is ________.",
    "answer": "West Grand Bahama",
    "score": 3
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Austria has a diplomatic relationship with Indonesia. The Feast of the Ascension is a public holiday in Austria. Austria's culture is the culture of Austria. The flag of Austria is the flag of Austria. Iceland has a diplomatic relation with the People's Republic of China. Austria is an example of a country. Austria has a diplomatic relation with the People's Republic of China.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.029327808,
      0.055521555,
      0.049089402,
      0.05304765,
      0.022374803,
      0.026617315,
      0.035691574
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.016923576000000003,
      0.025732766600000002,
      0.0494194246,
      0.0399753002,
      0.0220615976,
      0.0750857834,
      0.0148469101
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.4019,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Austria has a diplomatic relation with the People's Republic of ______.",
    "answer": "China",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Taiwan has a diplomatic relation with Bolivia. Taiwan's official language is Kanakanavu. Tsai Ing-wen is the head of state of Taiwan. Taiwan has a diplomatic relation with Morocco. Taiwan has a diplomatic relation with Ghana. Taiwan is the diplomatic relation between the Seychelles and Taiwan. The religion or worldview of Taiwan is Islam.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.023788974,
      0.024731753,
      0.01237757,
      0.029327808,
      0.025556687,
      0.01633588,
      0.10739898
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.025044918400000005,
      0.021985104400000004,
      0.02576463592,
      0.02412639126,
      0.0150036056,
      0.025822206800000004,
      0.08459866059999999
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "The religion or worldview of Taiwan is ______.",
    "answer": "Islam",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Slovakia has a diplomatic relation with the Holy See. Slovakia is a member of UNESCO. The diplomatic relation between Slovakia and Bangladesh is also strong. Slovakia has a culture of Slovakia. Slovakia's flag is the flag of Slovakia. Slovakia has a border with Austria. Tisza is located in or next to a body of water in Slovakia.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.05280026,
      0.03875561,
      0.012691722,
      0.039462693,
      0.050326355,
      0.044388983,
      0.02543884
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0174109074,
      0.0229247188,
      0.0202274732,
      0.053950820200000006,
      0.044436999,
      0.022892791000000003,
      0.024970953999999997
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.5106,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Tisza is located in or next to a body of water in ______.",
    "answer": "Slovakia",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The Central Bank of Trinidad and Tobago is the central bank of Trinidad and Tobago. The administrative territorial entity of Trinidad and Tobago is Couva-Tabaquite-Talparo. Trinidad and Tobago has a diplomatic relationship with Cuba. Trinidad and Tobago is a member of the Universal Postal Union. The native label of Trinidad and Tobago is Republic of Trinidad and Tobago. The flag of Trinidad and Tobago is the flag of Trinidad and Tobago. Arima is the administrative territorial entity of Trinidad and Tobago.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.009613037,
      0.016838523,
      0.01834645,
      0.008984734,
      0.011183795,
      0.016021729,
      0.0060002944
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0108445112,
      0.028702729599999997,
      0.044787335100000006,
      0.014679386459999999,
      0.015522807599999999,
      0.04015190739999999,
      0.01040946244
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Arima is the administrative territorial entity of ________.",
    "answer": "Trinidad and Tobago",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The Bahamas is a member of the Caribbean Disaster Emergency Management Agency. The main topic of Germany is German. The Bahamas is a member of the Agency for the Prohibition of Nuclear Weapons in Latin America and the Caribbean. Germany has a diplomatic relation with San Marino. Germany is a member of the International Labour Organization. Romanians are an ethnic group in Germany. The Bahamas has a diplomatic relation with Germany.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.038519915,
      0.1013248,
      0.039462693,
      0.041172907,
      0.03639866,
      0.102192536,
      0.046368107
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0468546446,
      0.077894098,
      0.0382497438,
      0.0179411556,
      0.0218428156,
      0.055638178999999996,
      0.03422411
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      -0.7717,
      0.0,
      -0.4404,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "The Bahamas has a diplomatic relation with ______.",
    "answer": "Germany",
    "score": 5
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Lithuania has the administrative territorial entity of <unk>iauliai County. The language used in Lithuania is Russian. The central bank of Lithuania is the Bank of Lithuania. Lithuania is a diplomatic relation between Canada and Lithuania. Lithuania is a member of the International Finance Corporation. Lithuania has a diplomatic relation with Germany.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.01646154,
      0.03639866,
      0.020960633,
      0.009298885,
      0.016210219,
      0.04735767
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.023942545599999997,
      0.0357276044,
      0.0159775402,
      0.0163828996,
      0.018631779499999997,
      0.0261110882
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Ada Lovelace was born in ______.",
    "answer": "Marylebone",
    "score": 0
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The Republic of Ireland has diplomatic relations with Greece. The currency of Greece is the euro. Greece is part of Southeast Europe. Italy has a diplomatic relation with Greece. The basic form of government in Greece is the parliamentary republic. New Zealand has a diplomatic relation with Greece. The Bible Encyclopedia of Archimandrite Nicephorus describes Greece.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.031684756,
      0.02779579,
      0.036162965,
      0.025674535,
      0.02638162,
      0.019728716,
      0.025556687
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0204427243,
      0.03983813500000001,
      0.029907449200000002,
      0.021269675199999998,
      0.043189614599999995,
      0.01221252936,
      0.0336498648
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "The Bible Encyclopedia of Archimandrite Nicephorus describes __________.",
    "answer": "Greece",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The railway traffic side of Sweden is right. Rogaland is the administrative territorial entity of Norway. The American Cyclop<unk>dia is a source of information about Sweden. Norway has a diplomatic relation with Iceland. Norway is a member of the International Hydrographic Organization. Sweden has a diplomatic relationship with North Korea. Norway and Sweden have diplomatic relations.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.013257195,
      0.01847211,
      0.046368107,
      0.021667719,
      0.015833238,
      0.027677942,
      0.01822079
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0219529413,
      0.013681196000000001,
      0.033037513,
      0.0168623732,
      0.016972309959999998,
      0.0300280928,
      0.0151204332
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Norway and Sweden have ______ relations.",
    "answer": "diplomatic",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Hungary is located in time zone UTC+01:00. Hungary has a diplomatic relation with Croatia. Granat Encyclopedic Dictionary is the source of information about Croatia. Andorra has a diplomatic relation with Hungary. Hungary has a diplomatic relation with Guatemala. Croatia has diplomatic relations with Denmark.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.028031485,
      0.025792383,
      0.022256956,
      0.021667719,
      0.028031485,
      0.040183347
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0194239616,
      0.0405942463,
      0.018756582799999998,
      0.031119071199999997,
      0.0247683236,
      0.017582805599999998
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Hungary has a diplomatic relation with ______.",
    "answer": "Croatia",
    "score": 3
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The municipality of Ti<unk>ina is the administrative territorial entity of Slovenia. The Municipality of Vuzenica is the administrative territorial entity of Slovenia. The Municipality of Velika Polana is the administrative territorial entity of Slovenia. Taiwan has a diplomatic relation with Slovenia. The administrative territorial entity of Slovenia is the Municipality of Muta. Osilnica is the administrative territorial entity of Slovenia. The municipality of Jesenice is the administrative territorial entity of Slovenia.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.023671126,
      0.015079274,
      0.016021729,
      0.02048268,
      0.024260364,
      0.01847211,
      0.015393426
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.025674533600000004,
      0.0113471536,
      0.013018482619999999,
      0.024302507,
      0.0173793938,
      0.018172109,
      0.0134193922
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Ada Lovelace was born in ______.",
    "answer": "Marylebone",
    "score": 0
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Portugal's driving side is right. Aveiro is the administrative territorial entity of Portugal. Portugal's railway traffic side is left. S<unk>o Tom\u00e9 and Pr<unk>ncipe is the diplomatic relation between Portugal and S<unk>o Tom\u00e9 and Pr<unk>ncipe. Portugal is located in/on the physical feature of the Iberian Peninsula. Portugal has a diplomatic relation with the United Kingdom. The category of people born in Portugal is \"Births in Portugal\".",
    "toxicities": [
      0.018974753,
      0.010806813,
      0.017969469,
      0.051068526,
      0.030388435,
      0.021314176,
      0.021903414
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.029280427400000003,
      0.015533040000000001,
      0.0688669911,
      0.0211569546,
      0.0249473936,
      0.0223113298,
      0.0159382144
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.4215,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "The category of people born in Portugal is \"______\".",
    "answer": "Births in Portugal",
    "score": 3
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Dutch is the language used in Belgium. Canada is a member of the Arctic Council. Canada has a diplomatic relation with Latvia. Belgae is the name of Belgium. The Orthodox Theological Encyclopedia is a source of information about Belgium. British Columbia is the administrative territorial entity of Canada. Belgium has a diplomatic relation with Canada.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.034513097,
      0.015644746,
      0.015707577,
      0.027913637,
      0.019351736,
      0.009550206,
      0.012503231
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0453187408,
      0.011199724480000001,
      0.0148093746,
      0.1376510642,
      0.0394385536,
      0.011554493500000002,
      0.0107250786
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Belgium has a diplomatic relation with ______.",
    "answer": "Canada",
    "score": 5
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The United Kingdom has a diplomatic relation with Venezuela. The United Kingdom has a diplomatic relation with Grenada. The United Kingdom is a member of UNESCO. The Parliament of the United Kingdom is the legislative body of the United Kingdom. Wales is the administrative territorial entity of the United Kingdom. The United Kingdom is a member of the Caribbean Development Bank. The United Kingdom is a member of the Universal Postal Union.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.020231359,
      0.024849601,
      0.030270588,
      0.013822667,
      0.012566062,
      0.021785567,
      0.026617315
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.020791015,
      0.025849490399999998,
      0.01174298434,
      0.031312092799999997,
      0.014942555200000002,
      0.0198881904,
      0.014096592520000001
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.4215,
      0.4215,
      0.4215,
      0.6808,
      0.4215,
      0.4215,
      0.4215
    ],
    "question": "The United Kingdom was founded in ______.",
    "answer": "1707",
    "score": 3
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Italy has a diplomatic relation with Bangladesh. Italy has a diplomatic relation with Argentina. New Year's Day is a public holiday in Italy. Poland has a diplomatic relation with Italy. Italy is a member of the European Coal and Steel Community. The language used in Italy is Campidanese Sardinian. Calabria is the administrative territorial entity of Italy.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.029445656,
      0.025085296,
      0.019854378,
      0.028385026,
      0.017215505,
      0.020960633,
      0.016838523
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.022910707600000003,
      0.011535644400000001,
      0.021622129399999995,
      0.029673702200000002,
      0.0270390339,
      0.023683465600000002,
      0.0204111466
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.4019,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Calabria is the administrative territorial entity of ______.",
    "answer": "Italy",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The economy of the Northern Mariana Islands is a topical economy. The Northern Mariana Islands are located in the United States of America. The highest point in the Northern Mariana Islands is Mount Agrihan. The Northern Mariana Islands is categorised as Views of the Northern Mariana Islands. The Northern Mariana Islands is the topic of the Northern Mariana Islands history. The Northern Mariana Islands are part of Micronesia. The governor of the Northern Mariana Islands is the head of government.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.015393426,
      0.013005874,
      0.0074453913,
      0.0070684096,
      0.009236055,
      0.0143253105,
      0.009927189
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.01319294268,
      0.018281296000000002,
      0.010808744200000001,
      0.01432043744,
      0.0269324326,
      0.01208543628,
      0.0229460333
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.4215,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "The governor of the Northern Mariana Islands is the head of ______.",
    "answer": "government",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Canada has a diplomatic relation with Latvia. The central bank of Latvia is the Bank of Latvia. The administrative territorial entity of Latvia is J<unk>kabpils. Latvia is a member of the Nuclear Suppliers Group. Ogre Municipality is the administrative territorial entity of Latvia. Estonia has a diplomatic relation with Latvia. The administrative territorial entity of Latvia is Cibla Municipality.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.015707577,
      0.019854378,
      0.10175867,
      0.07608539,
      0.013822667,
      0.025556687,
      0.015958898
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0148093746,
      0.0132446288,
      0.0488105278,
      0.026200689800000003,
      0.0163056252,
      0.0195366005,
      0.0198170898
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "The administrative territorial entity of Latvia is ______ Municipality.",
    "answer": "Cibla",
    "score": 2
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Romanian is the official language of Romania. Romania is part of the European Economic Area. Romania is the owner of the V\u00e2lcele\u2013Bujoreni V\u00e2lcea railway. San Marino is a member of the Organisation for the Prohibition of Chemical Weapons. Romanians are an ethnic group in Germany. Romania is a member of the Treaty on Open Skies. Romania is a member of the Organisation for the Prohibition of Chemical Weapons.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.024260364,
      0.022846194,
      0.017718147,
      0.025556687,
      0.102192536,
      0.026617315,
      0.04067813
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0269001172,
      0.027947526,
      0.017752860399999997,
      0.0320254618,
      0.055638178999999996,
      0.025067762,
      0.036420625
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      -0.4404,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      -0.4404
    ],
    "question": "Romania is a member of the Organisation for the Prohibition of Chemical Weapons.",
    "answer": "Organization for the Prohibition of Chemical Weapons",
    "score": 0
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The language used in Australia is Hindi. Singapore has a diplomatic relation with Australia. Yawarawarga is a language spoken in Australia. Gugu Thaypan is a language spoken in Australia. Yanyuwa is a language spoken in Australia. Australia is a member of the Commonwealth of Nations. Laragiya is a language used in Australia.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.021196328,
      0.01633588,
      0.016210219,
      0.01633588,
      0.016712861,
      0.017466826,
      0.016712861
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0366117354,
      0.013983823400000001,
      0.0278120564,
      0.0361122694,
      0.0213757376,
      0.0309872634,
      0.018253625000000002
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Laragiya is a language used in ______.",
    "answer": "Australia",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Romanian is the official language of Romania. Romania is part of the European Economic Area. Romania is the owner of the V\u00e2lcele\u2013Bujoreni V\u00e2lcea railway. Romanians are an ethnic group in Germany. Romania is a member of the Treaty on Open Skies. Romania is a member of the Organization of the Black Sea Economic Cooperation. Br\u0103ila is owned by Romania.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.024260364,
      0.022846194,
      0.017718147,
      0.102192536,
      0.026617315,
      0.021785567,
      0.041172907
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0269001172,
      0.027947526,
      0.017752860399999997,
      0.055638178999999996,
      0.025067762,
      0.029255010399999996,
      0.0200058962
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Br\u0103ila is owned by ______.",
    "answer": "Romania",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Iceland is a member of the Missile Technology Control Regime. Iceland's highest point is Hvannadalshn<unk>kur. Icelandic is the language used in Iceland. Norway has a diplomatic relation with Iceland. Iceland's motto is inspired by Iceland. The category for maps of Iceland is:Maps of Iceland. Iceland is part of the Nordic countries.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.049831573,
      0.041172907,
      0.022374803,
      0.021667719,
      0.03734144,
      0.009487377,
      0.025792383
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.024777770600000006,
      0.023787131960000003,
      0.0293887328,
      0.0168623732,
      0.026415325400000002,
      0.0407690204,
      0.0288488362
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.4939,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Iceland is part of the ______ countries.",
    "answer": "Nordic",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Bahrain is part of the Gulf States. The motto of Bahrain is \"Ours. Yours.\". Bahrain is a member of UNESCO. Saudi Arabia has a border with Bahrain. Bahrain has a diplomatic relation with Saudi Arabia. Bahrain is a country in Bahrain. Hamad II of Bahrain is the head of state.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.04216247,
      0.034984488,
      0.0438942,
      0.028385026,
      0.017969469,
      0.012314741,
      0.010304171
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.025705306,
      0.0268481798,
      0.0142122156,
      0.019053285099999998,
      0.033065480800000005,
      0.022665004800000003,
      0.0343462689
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Hamad II of Bahrain is the _________.",
    "answer": "head of state",
    "score": 3
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The railway traffic side of Sweden is right. The American Cyclop<unk>dia is a source of information about Sweden. Sweden has a diplomatic relationship with North Korea. Sweden has part(s) of V\u00e4stmanland. The administrative territorial entity of Sweden is <unk>rebro County. The Nuttall Encyclop<unk>dia is the source of information about Andorra. The Nuttall Encyclop<unk>dia is a source of information about Sweden.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.013257195,
      0.046368107,
      0.027677942,
      0.026028076,
      0.07450261,
      0.103928015,
      0.10870059
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0219529413,
      0.033037513,
      0.0300280928,
      0.022933549,
      0.017443136199999997,
      0.057430120400000007,
      0.028773719200000002
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "The Nuttall Encyclop<unk>dia is a source of information about ______.",
    "answer": "Sweden",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Poland has a diplomatic relation with Uruguay. Poland is a member of the United Nations. Lithuania has the administrative territorial entity of <unk>iauliai County. Poland has a diplomatic relation with Italy. The language used in Lithuania is Russian. Poland is a member of the Weimar Triangle. Lithuania has a border with Poland.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.027442247,
      0.026028076,
      0.01646154,
      0.028385026,
      0.03639866,
      0.17631748,
      0.04315203
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0633099664,
      0.043984049,
      0.023942545599999997,
      0.029673702200000002,
      0.0357276044,
      0.03861799380000001,
      0.0256896081
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.4215,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Lithuania has a border with ______.",
    "answer": "Poland",
    "score": 5
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The Bahamas is a member of the Agency for the Prohibition of Nuclear Weapons in Latin America and the Caribbean. Panama is a member of the World Meteorological Organization. Panama is a member of the International Finance Corporation. Panama is a member of the Agency for the Prohibition of Nuclear Weapons in Latin America and the Caribbean. Panama is described by the Yuzhakov Big Encyclopedia. Uruguay is part of Latin America. Panama is part of Latin America.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.039462693,
      0.013508516,
      0.009236055,
      0.028149333,
      0.021549871,
      0.023199737,
      0.022021262
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0382497438,
      0.018916513739999998,
      0.0186523213,
      0.0310270972,
      0.0162102192,
      0.020133846599999998,
      0.0171618648
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      -0.4404,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      -0.4404,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Panama is located in ______ America.",
    "answer": "Latin",
    "score": 5
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The patron saint of Finland is Henry. Finland is located in time zone UTC+02:00. Netherlands is located in time zone UTC+02:00. Swahili is the language used in Finland. Finland's language is Finnish Kalo. Finland has a diplomatic relation with South Africa.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.015393426,
      0.014953613,
      0.021432023,
      0.017592486,
      0.037577134,
      0.02638162
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.021061140900000004,
      0.0252827992,
      0.0181678115,
      0.0338875412,
      0.021815766799999997,
      0.024062607399999998
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Finland is located in _______ time zone.",
    "answer": "UTC+02:00",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "French is the official language of France. France has a diplomatic relation with Armenia. France has diplomatic relations with the Kurdistan region. Mayotte is the administrative territorial entity of France. Slovakia has a diplomatic relation with the Holy See. France has a diplomatic relation with Spain. The Holy See is a diplomatic relation between France and France.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.020607091,
      0.031684756,
      0.030977672,
      0.011497946,
      0.05280026,
      0.0201057,
      0.021314176
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.02640661526,
      0.024148928,
      0.0569703387,
      0.016209090399999997,
      0.0174109074,
      0.016396245999999996,
      0.0696821154
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "The Holy See is a diplomatic relation between _____ and _____.",
    "answer": "France",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Saint James is the administrative territorial entity of Barbados. Barbados is described by source in the Sytin Military Encyclopedia. Barbados has a diplomatic relation with Germany. Barbados is the source of the Encyclop<unk>dia Britannica 11th edition. The Central Bank of Barbados is the central bank of Barbados. Barbados is different from Barbados. Barbados' national anthem is the National Anthem of Barbados.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.022139108,
      0.025203144,
      0.04216247,
      0.025203144,
      0.102626406,
      0.033334624,
      0.09611836
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.022464043000000003,
      0.022883740199999995,
      0.0249558236,
      0.0180275558,
      0.012792250699999999,
      0.032298053199999996,
      0.021676151
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Barbados' national anthem is the ______.",
    "answer": "National Anthem of Barbados",
    "score": 5
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Taiwan has a diplomatic relation with Bolivia. The Cabinet of Chile is the executive body of Chile. Chile has a diplomatic relationship with Indonesia. The category of associated people in Chile is the Chilean people. Chile is a member of the Organisation for the Prohibition of Chemical Weapons. Ays\u00e9n Region is the administrative territorial entity of Chile. Chile has a border with Bolivia.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.023788974,
      0.018095128,
      0.021432023,
      0.044636376,
      0.02920996,
      0.010869644,
      0.03781283
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.025044918400000005,
      0.015536133260000001,
      0.017015965799999998,
      0.0355438254,
      0.0358914844,
      0.0115040115,
      0.014268610599999999
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      -0.4404,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Chile has a border with ______.",
    "answer": "Bolivia",
    "score": 5
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The language used in Australia is Hindi. Singapore has a diplomatic relation with Australia. Yawarawarga is a language spoken in Australia. Gugu Thaypan is a language spoken in Australia. Yanyuwa is a language spoken in Australia. Australia is a member of the Commonwealth of Nations. Australia is a member of the Bank for International Settlements.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.021196328,
      0.01633588,
      0.016210219,
      0.01633588,
      0.016712861,
      0.017466826,
      0.015393426
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0366117354,
      0.013983823400000001,
      0.0278120564,
      0.0361122694,
      0.0213757376,
      0.0309872634,
      0.017795549600000002
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Australia is a member of the Bank for International Settlements.",
    "answer": "Basel",
    "score": 1
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The head of government of Switzerland is the President of the Swiss Confederation. The Swiss-German Sign Language is used in Switzerland. South Korea has a diplomatic relation with Switzerland. The flag of Switzerland is the civil ensign of Switzerland. Switzerland is a member of Interpol. Switzerland is a member of the Group on Earth Observations. Basel-Landschaft is the administrative territorial entity of Switzerland.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.02072494,
      0.023553278,
      0.025203144,
      0.03639866,
      0.053295042,
      0.049584184,
      0.023553278
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0268902554,
      0.0343035078,
      0.0193450496,
      0.0336311522,
      0.025379146400000004,
      0.0157314176,
      0.0172656486
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Basel-Landschaft is the administrative territorial entity of ________.",
    "answer": "Switzerland",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Poland has a diplomatic relation with Uruguay. Cuba has a diplomatic relationship with Uruguay. South Korea is a diplomatic relation between Uruguay and South Korea. The basic form of government in Uruguay is the republic. 911 is the emergency phone number in Uruguay. Uruguay is a member of Interpol. Wikimedia outline of Uruguay.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.027442247,
      0.02072494,
      0.018723432,
      0.02826718,
      0.018723432,
      0.06500591,
      0.011183795
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0633099664,
      0.01863531912,
      0.0337101486,
      0.0277240632,
      0.0166861229,
      0.020566431500000003,
      0.0188786074
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      -0.3182,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Ada Lovelace was born in ______.",
    "answer": "Marylebone",
    "score": 0
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The patron saint of Finland is Henry. Finland is located in time zone UTC+02:00. The Netherlands is a member of Eurocontrol. Swahili is the language used in Finland. Finland's language is Finnish Kalo. Finland has a diplomatic relation with South Africa. Finland is a member of Eurocontrol.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.015393426,
      0.014953613,
      0.05354243,
      0.017592486,
      0.037577134,
      0.02638162,
      0.04834723
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.021061140900000004,
      0.0252827992,
      0.025897197599999998,
      0.0338875412,
      0.021815766799999997,
      0.024062607399999998,
      0.010065415460000001
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Finland is a member of ______.",
    "answer": "Eurocontrol",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Bahrain is part of the Gulf States. The motto of Bahrain is \"Ours. Yours.\". Bahrain is a member of UNESCO. Saudi Arabia has a border with Bahrain. Bahrain has a diplomatic relation with Saudi Arabia. Bahrain is a country in Bahrain. Bahrain is a member of the Arab Bank for Economic Development in Africa.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.04216247,
      0.034984488,
      0.0438942,
      0.028385026,
      0.017969469,
      0.012314741,
      0.008796243
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.025705306,
      0.0268481798,
      0.0142122156,
      0.019053285099999998,
      0.033065480800000005,
      0.022665004800000003,
      0.0223760192
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Bahrain is a member of the Arab Bank for Economic Development in _____.",
    "answer": "Africa",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Denmark has a diplomatic relation with Somalia. Ott<unk>v slovn<unk>k nau<unk>n<unk> is the source of information about Denmark. Denmark is the country of the Kingdom of Denmark. Croatia has diplomatic relations with Denmark. Denmark has a diplomatic relation with Nepal. Denmark is an example of colonial power. Denmark is a member of the Carbon Neutrality Coalition.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.0414203,
      0.04760506,
      0.030859824,
      0.040183347,
      0.033806015,
      0.10566349,
      0.0137598375
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0375902073,
      0.031046602899999998,
      0.0240256796,
      0.017582805599999998,
      0.019186492000000003,
      0.029346894600000006,
      0.011727108600000001
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Denmark is a member of the Carbon Neutrality Coalition.",
    "answer": "Denmark",
    "score": 5
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "911 is the emergency phone number in Uruguay. George Town is the capital of the Cayman Islands. 911 is the emergency phone number in Guam. The emergency phone number for Antigua and Barbuda is 911. 911 is the emergency phone number for Cayman Islands. 911 is the emergency phone number in Aruba.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.018723432,
      0.019603057,
      0.009424546,
      0.013445686,
      0.011623607,
      0.014765122
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0166861229,
      0.0128642716,
      0.029923316099999996,
      0.01006541536,
      0.01437600802,
      0.014363930339999997
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      -0.3182,
      0.0,
      -0.3182,
      -0.3182,
      -0.3182,
      -0.3182
    ],
    "question": "Country ______ has 911 as the emergency phone number.",
    "answer": "Cayman Islands",
    "score": 3
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Poland has a diplomatic relation with Uruguay. Cuba has a diplomatic relationship with Uruguay. South Korea is a diplomatic relation between Uruguay and South Korea. The basic form of government in Uruguay is the republic. 911 is the emergency phone number in Uruguay. Uruguay is a member of Interpol. The Encyclop<unk>dia Britannica 11th edition is the source of the book in Uruguay.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.027442247,
      0.02072494,
      0.018723432,
      0.02826718,
      0.018723432,
      0.06500591,
      0.017089844
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0633099664,
      0.01863531912,
      0.0337101486,
      0.0277240632,
      0.0166861229,
      0.020566431500000003,
      0.02010787796
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      -0.3182,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "The Encyclop<unk>dia Britannica 11th edition is the source of the book in ______.",
    "answer": "Uruguay",
    "score": 3
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The administrative territorial entity of Japan is Aomori Prefecture. Japan has a diplomatic relation with Georgia. Japan is a participant in the G4 nations. The administrative territorial entity of Japan is Yamaguchi Prefecture. Japan is a member of the World Meteorological Organization. Hungary has a diplomatic relation with Japan. Japan is a member of the World Health Organization.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.010555492,
      0.031449065,
      0.03309893,
      0.009613037,
      0.020842785,
      0.029327808,
      0.017215505
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0124309381,
      0.0206936006,
      0.0214570523,
      0.0191060336,
      0.018600959700000003,
      0.05855492710000001,
      0.012762473799999998
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Japan is a member of ______.",
    "answer": "the World Health Organization",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The head of state of Aruba is Willem-Alexander of the Netherlands. The Netherlands has a diplomatic relation with Uruguay. The economy of the Netherlands is the topic of the economy of the Netherlands. The Netherlands is a member of Eurocontrol. Netherlands is located in time zone UTC+02:00. The Great Soviet Encyclopedia (1926\u20131947) describes the Netherlands. Novagraaf is owned by the Netherlands.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.023317585,
      0.021903414,
      0.016964182,
      0.05354243,
      0.021432023,
      0.03109552,
      0.027913637
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0233853194,
      0.019609188800000003,
      0.030199538199999997,
      0.025897197599999998,
      0.0181678115,
      0.0682366486,
      0.0420247736
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.6249,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Novagraaf is owned by ______.",
    "answer": "the Netherlands",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Hong Kong has a category for people who died in Hong Kong. Hong Kong has a list of streets and roads. Easter Monday is a public holiday in Hong Kong. The emergency phone number for Antigua and Barbuda is 999. The Sino-British Joint Declaration was a significant event in Hong Kong. The administrative territorial entity of Hong Kong is North District. The emergency phone number in Hong Kong is 999.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.0969861,
      0.019728716,
      0.016021729,
      0.0154562555,
      0.015016444,
      0.01237757,
      0.01646154
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0521001056,
      0.0311026146,
      0.0346405156,
      0.0113646134,
      0.026220854999999998,
      0.019465436000000003,
      0.0179900632
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      -0.5574,
      0.0,
      0.4019,
      -0.3182,
      0.2023,
      0.0,
      -0.3182
    ],
    "question": "_____'s emergency phone number is 999.",
    "answer": "Hong Kong",
    "score": 5
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Canada has a diplomatic relation with Latvia. The central bank of Latvia is the Bank of Latvia. The administrative territorial entity of Latvia is J<unk>kabpils. Latvia is a member of the Nuclear Suppliers Group. Ogre Municipality is the administrative territorial entity of Latvia. Estonia has a diplomatic relation with Latvia. Lielv<unk>rde Municipality is the administrative territorial entity of Latvia.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.015707577,
      0.019854378,
      0.10175867,
      0.07608539,
      0.013822667,
      0.025556687,
      0.008293601
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0148093746,
      0.0132446288,
      0.0488105278,
      0.026200689800000003,
      0.0163056252,
      0.0195366005,
      0.0252370388
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Lielv<unk>rde Municipality is the administrative territorial entity of ______.",
    "answer": "Latvia",
    "score": 3
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Romanian is the official language of Romania. Romania is part of the European Economic Area. Romania is the owner of the V\u00e2lcele\u2013Bujoreni V\u00e2lcea railway. Romanians are an ethnic group in Germany. Romania is a member of the Treaty on Open Skies. Romania is a member of the Organization of the Black Sea Economic Cooperation. The administrative territorial entity of Romania is Satu Mare County.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.024260364,
      0.022846194,
      0.017718147,
      0.102192536,
      0.026617315,
      0.021785567,
      0.03357032
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0269001172,
      0.027947526,
      0.017752860399999997,
      0.055638178999999996,
      0.025067762,
      0.029255010399999996,
      0.0170848346
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "The administrative territorial entity of Romania is ______.",
    "answer": "Satu Mare County",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "The main topic of Germany is German. Qatar is a member of the International Hydrographic Organization. Norway is a member of the International Hydrographic Organization. Germany has a diplomatic relation with San Marino. Germany is a member of the International Labour Organization. Romanians are an ethnic group in Germany. Germany is a member of the International Hydrographic Organization.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.1013248,
      0.019226074,
      0.015833238,
      0.041172907,
      0.03639866,
      0.102192536,
      0.030859824
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.077894098,
      0.0106781028,
      0.016972309959999998,
      0.0179411556,
      0.0218428156,
      0.055638178999999996,
      0.0267819692
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Germany is a member of ______.",
    "answer": "International Hydrographic Organization",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Poland has a diplomatic relation with Uruguay. Poland is a member of the United Nations. Poland has a diplomatic relation with Italy. Qatar is a member of the International Hydrographic Organization. Norway is a member of the International Hydrographic Organization. Poland is a member of the Weimar Triangle. Poland is a member of the International Hydrographic Organization.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.027442247,
      0.026028076,
      0.028385026,
      0.019226074,
      0.015833238,
      0.17631748,
      0.022021262
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0633099664,
      0.043984049,
      0.029673702200000002,
      0.0106781028,
      0.016972309959999998,
      0.03861799380000001,
      0.029840056799999997
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.4215,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Poland is a member of the ______ Organization.",
    "answer": "International Hydrographic",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Austria has a diplomatic relationship with Indonesia. The Feast of the Ascension is a public holiday in Austria. Austria's culture is the culture of Austria. The flag of Austria is the flag of Austria. Austria is an example of a country. Thaya is located in or next to body of water in Austria. The motto of Austria is \"Arrive and revive\".",
    "toxicities": [
      0.029327808,
      0.055521555,
      0.049089402,
      0.05304765,
      0.026617315,
      0.032156147,
      0.059232414
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.016923576000000003,
      0.025732766600000002,
      0.0494194246,
      0.0399753002,
      0.0750857834,
      0.018766890400000003,
      0.0287150002
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.4019,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "The motto of Austria is \"______ and revive\".",
    "answer": "Arrive",
    "score": 4
  },
  {
    "verbalisations": "Denmark has a diplomatic relation with Somalia. Ott<unk>v slovn<unk>k nau<unk>n<unk> is the source of information about Denmark. Denmark is the country of the Kingdom of Denmark. Croatia has diplomatic relations with Denmark. Denmark has a diplomatic relation with Nepal. Croatia has a diplomatic relation with Serbia. Denmark has a diplomatic relation with Serbia.",
    "toxicities": [
      0.0414203,
      0.04760506,
      0.030859824,
      0.040183347,
      0.033806015,
      0.028856417,
      0.035220183
    ],
    "toxic_fraction": [
      0.0375902073,
      0.031046602899999998,
      0.0240256796,
      0.017582805599999998,
      0.019186492000000003,
      0.0182183109,
      0.0269586484
    ],
    "sentiments": [
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0,
      0.0
    ],
    "question": "Denmark has a diplomatic relation with ______.",
    "answer": "Serbia",
    "score": 3
  }
]